<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TrafficStopQuestions>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="~y~TRAFFIC STOP: AUTHORIZATION~s~">
    <!-- Existing Questions -->
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SEARCH] Do I have your consent to search the vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you may search the vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to a vehicle search.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you need to search my vehicle?</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand, but I do not consent to a search.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to speak to my lawyer before consenting.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SEARCH] Do I have your consent to search you?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you can search me.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to a personal search.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you want to search me?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not comfortable with that, so I decline.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to speak to my lawyer before consenting.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SEARCH] Do I have your consent to search your home?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you may search my home.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to a home search.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you need to search my home?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I see a warrant before I agree to a search?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to speak to a lawyer before consenting to this search.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SEARCH] Do I have your consent to search your property?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you may search my property.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to a property search.</Answer>
        <Answer>What exactly are you looking for?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you have a warrant to search my property?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to consult with a lawyer before agreeing to this search.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[TEST] Do you consent to a Breathalyzer test?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, I consent to the Breathalyzer test.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to the Breathalyzer test.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I have the right to refuse the test?</Answer>
        <Answer>What happens if I refuse the test?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I speak to a lawyer before deciding?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[TEST] Do you consent to a Narcotics test?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, I consent to the Narcotics test.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to the Narcotics test.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I have the right to refuse the test?</Answer>
        <Answer>What happens if I refuse the test?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I speak to a lawyer before deciding?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[TEST] Do you consent to a Field Sobriety test?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, I consent to the Field Sobriety test.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to the Field Sobriety test.</Answer>
        <Answer>What does the test involve?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I have the right to refuse the test?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I speak to a lawyer before deciding?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[ENTRY] May I step inside your house?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you may come in.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent to you entering my home.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you need to come inside?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd prefer to keep the conversation outside.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to speak to a lawyer before allowing you inside.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[ENTRY] May I enter your home due to an emergency?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, you may come in if it's an emergency.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I do not consent even if it's an emergency.</Answer>
        <Answer>What's the emergency?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can we handle this outside?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to know more before I let you in.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[WARRANT] May I enter your home with this warrant?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, I understand and you may enter.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I still do not consent.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I see the warrant first?</Answer>
        <Answer>Let me consult my lawyer before you enter.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can we discuss this before you come in?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: INTRO">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Introduction~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Good Morning/Afternoon/Evening</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I made more money on unemployment than going to my job, I'm pissed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm all out of doughnuts and coffee sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Morning officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ineed it's a very good morning.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just on my way to hot yoga but you don't care do you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Good morning to you too.</Answer>
        <Answer>Another day in paradise. I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a feeling it's going to get worse.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, The Lord is good.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way to go score some weed.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I was on welfare I could be asleep right now huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way to my corporate prison, I mean work.</Answer>
        <Answer>Out of all mornings you pick THIS one!</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear you have the worst timing ever!</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh-huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good morning to you as well.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just minding my own business, you should try it.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, no, no, I don't have time for this.</Answer>
        <Answer>i can't be late again I am going to be so screwed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, I guess if you want to call it good.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew you were going to stop me..I JUST KNEW IT!</Answer>
        <Answer>How can I help you this lovely morning?</Answer>
        <Answer>You don't have coronavirus do you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Nice day out officer, How may I assist you?</Answer>
        <Answer>I should still be sleeping ugggh!</Answer>
        <Answer>It's just waaaay too early for me right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Would be better if I wasn't being pulled over.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not a morning person sorry, haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>I do love the mornings, it's good to be alive.</Answer>
        <Answer>I owe, I owe, So off to work I go.</Answer>
        <Answer>I legally have to tell you I've been exposed to coronavirus.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't know about you but I don't want to go to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm loving that the traffic is not so bad today.</Answer>
        <Answer>If it isn't the long strong arm of the law!</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm in such a good mood even you can't ruin it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well, what do I owe the pleasure officer?</Answer>
        <Answer>My brother works for the LSPD I wonder if you know him?</Answer>
        <Answer>I get so damn nervous when you guys follow me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Howdy officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>It will be, once I get me some coffee.</Answer>
        <Answer>Does Taco Bell still serve the breakfast waffle?</Answer>
        <Answer>I worked all night, I hate graveyard shifts.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Glares at you*</Answer>
        <Answer>I was really hoping your lights weren't for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you know Sgt.Peters? He's my my uncle.</Answer>
        <Answer>Lordy,Lordy, what did I do this time?</Answer>
        <Answer>We need to go back in to lockdown, the traffic was so great.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you don't want coronavirus I suggest you get back to your cruiser</Answer>
        <Answer>Crazy times we're living in huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can we make this like lightning fast? I'm in a hurry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Morning, I hope you are having a good shift.</Answer>
        <Answer>This sucks, I miss working from home.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm guessing you wanted to give me an encouraging speech today?</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew you were going to stop me...and here we are.</Answer>
        <Answer>How can I help you this lovely morning?</Answer>
        <Answer>And what do I owe this untimely pleasure?</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't shoot! LOL just kidding.</Answer>
        <Answer>Told myself it's too early to get tazed, guess I was wrong.</Answer>
        <Answer>How's it going officer?</Answer>
        <Answer>Just got done with the gym, burned off some of that quarantine weight.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just so you know you're being recorded for my safety.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is this where I start recording?</Answer>
        <Answer>I see I'm starting the day off just great.</Answer>
        <Answer>I overslept and rushed out the door, still not fully awake.</Answer>
        <Answer>Quarantine was great for me, I miss sleeping in don't you?</Answer>
        <Answer>If all the officers looked like you I'd get stopped everyday.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look who it is San Andrea's finest essential workers.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks at you*</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh how I miss the unemployment checks.</Answer>
        <Answer>Officer..</Answer>
        <Answer>I would not want to have your job now days.. haha</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks around*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Gives you a smirk*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm good but my hands are shaking haha. You crept up on me </Answer>
        <Answer>Morning officer, I hope that all is well with you today.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just asking myself If I took care of any warrants.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I've been better.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm starving and headed to get some lunch.</Answer>
        <Answer>I've been fighting the flu all week officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nervous, not sure If I have all my paperwork.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just buried my brother today not that you care.</Answer>
        <Answer>Awesome just on the way to the.. nevermind.</Answer>
        <Answer>Eh.. yourself?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be better once I make it to the plug.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just out for a quick lunch break from work.</Answer>
        <Answer>Going home sick from work, I might have that coronavirus haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Feeling pretty amazing today, I got a raise at work.</Answer>
        <Answer>My kid just got suspended from school, so not well.</Answer>
        <Answer>This hottie hit on me at the gym, it made my day.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really don't care for small talk.</Answer>
        <Answer>You trying to get my number, I wouldn't be mad if you were.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm blessed, just like all of God's children.</Answer>
        <Answer>Going to meet up with a hot date.</Answer>
        <Answer>It has been a tough week I wont lie.</Answer>
        <Answer>I legally have to tell you I've been exposed to coronavirus.</Answer>
        <Answer>Doing wonderful and yourself?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well the idiots that changed my oil forgot to put the plug in.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way to go pick up a delicious Pizza from Mama Johns.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just out for a quick drive to the traphouse.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's a beautiful day so I can't complain.</Answer>
        <Answer>What do you want?</Answer>
        <Answer>Same ole Same ole, I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tired, just really tired.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ready for work to be done so I can go home.</Answer>
        <Answer>I've been so bored all day.</Answer>
        <Answer>Still shook about Kobe being dead, Lakers won it all though.</Answer>
        <Answer>My whole family has been sick, be careful you don't catch it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Need to beat a porch pirate to my house trying to steal my package.</Answer>
        <Answer>My Ring alarm alerted me someone just came to my doorstep.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just living life.</Answer>
        <Answer>So awesome!</Answer>
        <Answer>Given everyone is looking at us I'm embarrassed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wonderful, I hope you're doing well.</Answer>
        <Answer>I must say you look sharp in that uniform.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is rediculous don't you think?</Answer>
        <Answer>Regretting going back to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so hungry, I couldn't get away to take lunch.</Answer>
        <Answer>My son is flying in today and I'm excited to see him.</Answer>
        <Answer>I exist that's all I can say.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sad, just lost my mother this morning to coronavirus.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not bad at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way to cash my welfare check.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that your tactic for putting me at ease?</Answer>
        <Answer>Jesus! You're going to make me late.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have an appointment with a realtor I'd like to make.</Answer>
        <Answer>Blessings my child, Kifflom in the name of Epsilon.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm doing good I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm alright I have just been stir crazy during the lockdown.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, how are you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I assume I did something wrong?</Answer>
        <Answer>Still paying taxes to put food on your table. So yeah.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Hello, you're quite the good looking cop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you have snap chat babe?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure you'd rather be eating lunch and not dealing with me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh lucky me. I got the hot cop today.</Answer>
        <Answer>Stupendously wonderful I suppose.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hunny, you're killing that uniform.</Answer>
        <Answer>My stomach dropped once you lit me up haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's been 6 months and counting since Kobe passed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Traffic stops are just so embarrassing, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I haven't caught coronavirus yet so.. Im pretty good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just getting over that covid-19, handled it like a champ.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Cries uncontrollably*</Answer>
        <Answer>Just wondering when I can work again, I can't afford this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance you have the wrong person?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks up* Why do you do this to me Lord?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm single and ready to mingle, if you're interested.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trying to get used to all this traffic again, it sucks.</Answer>
        <Answer>Kifflom to you my child, do you follow the teachings of Epsilom?</Answer>
        <Answer>None of the stores are open and i need to buy a laptop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't you have a lunchbreak soon, I know I'd like to take mine.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just had the kluckin bell chicken sandwhich, way better than Popeye's.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just go ahead and tell them your're 10-8, I won't tell.</Answer>
        <Answer>You have no reason to be stopping me...UNBELIEVABLE!</Answer>
        <Answer>Just great!</Answer>
        <Answer>Just give me my ticket and let me be on my way.</Answer>
        <Answer>You and I need to hang out and have a few shots.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is it a bribe if I want to buy you a beer as a thank you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh, the fun we're about to have.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hi, aren't you just the cutest thing ever.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh my I got lucky for once and got the hot cop!</Answer>
        <Answer>As soon as you lit me up my heart dropped!</Answer>
        <Answer>*Rolls eyes*</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a feeling it's going to get worse.</Answer>
        <Answer>Only those who follow Epsilon are truly good.</Answer>
        <Answer>I legally have to tell you I've been exposed to coronavirus.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm such a loser, another lonely night.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was until my friend got shot in Strawberry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure is a fine night for a party.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have seen you before, do you always work nights?</Answer>
        <Answer>I appreciate you not shining your flashlight in my face.</Answer>
        <Answer>Evening, morning, who the hell cares.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, it's a beautiful night.</Answer>
        <Answer>Goodness, this is so annoying.</Answer>
        <Answer>It is huh? Such a great evening.</Answer>
        <Answer>Covid has killed my dating life.. this sucks!</Answer>
        <Answer>It is waaaay too late for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Evening to you as well.</Answer>
        <Answer>Only thing open this late is bars and legs, I like both.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good I got no reason to be nervous.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just trying to get home to get some sleep.</Answer>
        <Answer>For what do I owe the pleasure?</Answer>
        <Answer>Evening officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I do for you this evening?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so sick of meeting people online because of covid.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just like you I'm on my way to start the night shift at work.</Answer>
        <Answer>Gonna be late for my Tinder date if we don't hurry this up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Your lights are blinding me can you turn them off?</Answer>
        <Answer>Cute aren't you special, what can I do for you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Depends on if I get to leave in my own car.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew I should have taken a side street.</Answer>
        <Answer>My life is like flashing before my eyes.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh Huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Does my vehicle smell to you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Out of all of the cars you stop mine!</Answer>
        <Answer>Meeting a date from Bumble since that's the norm now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Every evening is the same to me, so whats up?</Answer>
        <Answer>This is the first date I've been on in ages, Hi cutie.</Answer>
        <Answer>Excited to have a night out with my friends.</Answer>
        <Answer>The kids have a sitter and I'm going out.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh I'm so ready to party...responsibly of course.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you know of any good restaurants, I have the munchies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh my you scared me a moment ago, what can I do for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha, you got me and I was even looking for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look, I'll be more careful I promise.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear this happens everytime I'm in this part of town.</Answer>
        <Answer>Now I have to explain to my date why I'm late.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, okay, good evening.</Answer>
        <Answer>Mhhhmmm.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's pretty sad when a night out is going to the grocery store.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, it is and I'm out of condoms so pardon the rush.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just out to grab a quick bite and heading home.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well aren't you just the cutest thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>The weather could change though, whether I have drugs or not.</Answer>
        <Answer>I try my hardest to avoid you pigs.</Answer>
        <Answer>Got people all around us recording me on their cellphones!</Answer>
        <Answer>Yip, if you say so.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just need to get home ASAP.</Answer>
        <Answer>I appreciate you keeping us all safe, thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>The internet is the only thing holding society together. Am I right?</Answer>
        <Answer>I might be getting arrested tonight, you're looking too fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have hand sanitizer in my glove box if you need it.</Answer>
        <Answer>WHERE IS YOUR MASK?</Answer>
        <Answer>The Casino is finally opened back up, I'm lit.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you know how bad I want to go to a bar and just dance?</Answer>
        <Answer>Just aimlessly wondering for a late night snack.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear those lights will give someone a heart attack.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hahaha I knew you seen me! whats good with ya?</Answer>
        <Answer>I ordered doordash and STILL had to go get my food. USELESS!</Answer>
        <Answer>Pizza delivery is a 2 hour wait! I can't wait that long.</Answer>
        <Answer>This quarantine sucks, my kids are driving me nuts.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Any idea why i stopped you just now?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I don't have the slightest clue.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure you will make something up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I forget to signal my turn or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>You watched me leave the Krispy Kreme?</Answer>
        <Answer>You smelled my fresh coffee?</Answer>
        <Answer>To tell me I broke one of the million laws in this city?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm hoping to give me some driving tips.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope, but have at it officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are we still under lockdown or something? I forget.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know a mask is required in public but I forgot it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Was it because I checked my phone a few times?</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I run a light?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope I didn't hit someone.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm at a total loss.</Answer>
        <Answer>To thank me for being an essential worker like you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Speeding.. definitley speeding.</Answer>
        <Answer>You thought I was cute and wanted to say Hi?</Answer>
        <Answer>Why would you ask if you thought I knew?</Answer>
        <Answer>To pay your respects to my dead grandmother?</Answer>
        <Answer>Needed to boost your ego some?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Groans*</Answer>
        <Answer>You thought I was sexy and wanted to say hi?</Answer>
        <Answer>I know you were not pleased with my driving.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hell if I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't think of any legal reason so?</Answer>
        <Answer>Please do inform me.</Answer>
        <Answer>To pay your respects to KOBE like I'm doing?</Answer>
        <Answer>I got a list but we'll see what you choose.</Answer>
        <Answer>I bet it's that damn headlight huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods No*</Answer>
        <Answer>I may have been texting a bit.</Answer>
        <Answer>I get told I look like a celebrity, can you guess which one?</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope, please enlighten me.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, but I cant wait to hear it.</Answer>
        <Answer>You thought I was a grub-hub with dunkin doughuts?</Answer>
        <Answer>You smelled my fresh coffee?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am hoping to give me some driving tips.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope but have at it officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Surprise me because I'm cluless.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh.. what could it be now?</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a few ideas haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>You heard I was newly single?</Answer>
        <Answer>To waste my gas which cost a rediculous amount in this state?</Answer>
        <Answer>It would seem something about my driving upset you.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's me! Do you not recognize me I live down the block.</Answer>
        <Answer>I promise you I don't care.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I look like I graduated from a community college like you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Hell yeah I watch Live PD everynight.</Answer>
        <Answer>You need a good bust so your boss will be happy?</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't signal my turn, is that it?</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't care my spouse is a doctor and saves lives.</Answer>
        <Answer>You wanted to thank me for my essential service?</Answer>
        <Answer>To show me not all cops are bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is it because I maybe littered?</Answer>
        <Answer>No telling with you pigs.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will not incriminate myself.</Answer>
        <Answer>Show off the ride my tax dollars paid for?</Answer>
        <Answer>Because you don't think I can afford this car?</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe because this area is known for narcotics?</Answer>
        <Answer>Considering you didn't stop anyone but me..No.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I can't say that I do.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is a fun game, I always try to guess before you ask.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have done so much stuff, It could be anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>It could be literally ANYTHING!</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, I'm pretty sure I know exactly why.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I know exactly why.</Answer>
        <Answer>Was my music too loud or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>You were lonely and wanted a friend to chat with?</Answer>
        <Answer>You were bored?</Answer>
        <Answer>No.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope it's nothing bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh i think i do haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>I looked like an easy target?</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh.. I sure would like to know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't say I do off hand.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wish I knew.</Answer>
        <Answer>I gotta go with racial profiling.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm pretty sure you're going to tell me though.</Answer>
        <Answer>To let me know I'm an oustanding driver?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope it's nothing bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm not sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was having a little too much fun back there?</Answer>
        <Answer>You're jealous of my ride?</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah and I dont really care.</Answer>
        <Answer>You wanted to trigger my epilepsy with your lights?</Answer>
        <Answer>Gee, I have no clue.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, Yep, but lets see if we both think the same.</Answer>
        <Answer>As soon as I did it I knew you saw me.</Answer>
        <Answer>As the Lord lives I do not know.</Answer>
        <Answer>You didn't want to do real police work?</Answer>
        <Answer>Using me as an excuse to take a break?</Answer>
        <Answer>Doesn't matter, I love talking to you officers.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess My vehicle says I'm made out of money!</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a horrible memory, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>To hassle ppor innocent civilians.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure, I was just minding my own business.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Identify Yourself~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm officer ___________.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>One of this departments finest.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks at you*</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I do for you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank goodness you're here.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm ______ good to meet you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good to meet you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hi.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hey it's great to see you.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm deputy ___________.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Umm..</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I do for you deputy?</Answer>
        <Answer>It's great to see you.</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I do for you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Let me know how I can be of service.</Answer>
        <Answer>What brings you around these parts?</Answer>
        <Answer>Hey deputy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hi..</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm ____ good to meet you.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm trooper ___________.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Hello.</Answer>
        <Answer>So happy to see you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Howdy!</Answer>
        <Answer>It's a pleasure.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's great to see you.</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I do for you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Hi trooper ___.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh boy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I help you?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Introduction Questions~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Why did you take so long to pull over?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>How fast am I supposed to pullover geeze?</Answer>
        <Answer>I was trying to find a spot we could both fit. Giggity!</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I really? I didn't think it was that long.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was so nervous with all your lights behind me.</Answer>
        <Answer>The ground was moving really fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be honest my stomach dropped and I was scared.</Answer>
        <Answer>My hope was that you would drive around me. </Answer>
        <Answer>Relax, I was finishing a tweet.</Answer>
        <Answer>I couldn't find the turn signal in this thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't know I was being timed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was hoping you weren't stopping me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I get stopped a lot and no other officers complained.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was just hard to see, I didn't want to hit something.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was giving you the opportunity to go around me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really didn't want to get a ticket today.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's just how I usually stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>You waste my time so I like to waste some of yours.</Answer>
        <Answer>This cute face gets me nothing but warnings.</Answer>
        <Answer>Making sure my lawyer was on speakerphone.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh, it's just my way of wasting some of your time.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't know.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Where are you headed?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Just about to get a sprunk at the LTD.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will remain silent on this one, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have an important audition for a TV show at the studio.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way to Rockford Hills finest sex club.</Answer>
        <Answer>Down to mission row to help feed the homeless.</Answer>
        <Answer>All out of weed, so about to go grab a few ounces.</Answer>
        <Answer>My daughter was killed so I'm going to ID the body.</Answer>
        <Answer>24/7 store to get a coffee, you want one?</Answer>
        <Answer>I needed to talk to some ladies at the Vanilla Unicorn.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at Life Invader.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just out for a little joyride.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think it finally got me! Going to get a covid test.</Answer>
        <Answer>Possibly prison after this traffic stop, haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Going fishing at the National Park.</Answer>
        <Answer>Meeting with my realtor to look at a house.</Answer>
        <Answer>Headed down to the pawnshop in Davis.</Answer>
        <Answer>I need coffee.. that's where I am going.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wherever Google maps takes me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm meeting some friends down at the Pier.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way home because I forgot my debit card.</Answer>
        <Answer>Rockford Hills for some shoplifting...I mean shopping.</Answer>
        <Answer>My sister lives in Mirror Park.</Answer>
        <Answer>A friend got an Air Bnb and we're going to PARTAAY!</Answer>
        <Answer>Get some grocercies before idiots panic buy everything.</Answer>
        <Answer>Grove Street to take care of some business.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure what I want to eat so I'm just cruising around.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm on thr way to the hospital to get a covid test.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm meeting up with an old flame at the Hen House.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm craving some tacos from the taco truck.</Answer>
        <Answer>My grandmother's house in Grapeseed.</Answer>
        <Answer>On my way home because I forgot my phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just going to the church praise Jesus.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was out getting some smokes.</Answer>
        <Answer>Spent some time at the lake.</Answer>
        <Answer>I rented an Air BnB on the coast by the lighthouse.</Answer>
        <Answer>U tool is having a sale so I'm headed there.</Answer>
        <Answer>About to have a family get-together.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm meeting my sister in Vinewood to see the walk of fame.</Answer>
        <Answer>Going to see Kat Williams at the comedy club.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just out to pick up my perscription.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hoping to visit the dealership and trade in this bucket.</Answer>
        <Answer>Headed to Paleto Bay, I rented an Air BnB on the coast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Eh it is not interesting anyway.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry,I don't just give out my plans.</Answer>
        <Answer>My computer died so I am going to the mall to get a new one.</Answer>
        <Answer>My friend was in an accident and I'm going to see them.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Where are you coming from?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That ain't none yo damn business.</Answer>
        <Answer>The Kluckin Bell to get an amazing Chicken Sandwich.</Answer>
        <Answer>Doing a grocery run, that EBT hit today.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just auditioned for a movie.</Answer>
        <Answer>My mom's house down in Davis.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just picked up my sister from the airport.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had a tour of the movie set down in the city.</Answer>
        <Answer>My brother's wedding, he rented a private yacht.</Answer>
        <Answer>My personal endeavours are not up for discussion.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was out getting some smokes.</Answer>
        <Answer>Spent some time at the lake.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just hanging out at my BFF's.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at the Maze Arena.</Answer>
        <Answer>I worked out at the gym, all about that fit life.</Answer>
        <Answer>The airport if you must know, you nosey cop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Spent some time at the lake.</Answer>
        <Answer>My boss wanted to show off his Yatch to us poor folks.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just a couple blocks down the road.</Answer>
        <Answer>Had a business meeting with some partners.</Answer>
        <Answer>My brother lives in Idaho so I took him to the airport.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was hanging out with a couple of co-workers.</Answer>
        <Answer>Spent most the day at the beach.</Answer>
        <Answer>Paid respects to Kobe at the Maze Bank Arena.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was meeting the family for a picnic.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just got back from visiting my sister in Texas.</Answer>
        <Answer>Vangelico's jewlery to get something.</Answer>
        <Answer>My brother lives in Mirror Park.</Answer>
        <Answer>Grove Street to hang out with the homies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Heaven on earth, the Vanilla Unicorn.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had to fill up the ride with some gasoline.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just grabbing a bite to eat.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hitting up the movies in Mission Row.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just got done with a booty call.</Answer>
        <Answer>My aunt from Florida visited, so I took her to LSIA.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dropped a friend off at the courthouse.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just finished up my shift at work.</Answer>
        <Answer>A date, if that is okay with you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm coming back from a photo-shoot.</Answer>
        <Answer>Dropped a friend off at the bus stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't worry about it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really don't see how that is relevant to the stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was out getting some smokes.</Answer>
        <Answer>A friend and I were doing some lingerie shopping.</Answer>
        <Answer>Spent some time at Fort Zancudo.</Answer>
        <Answer>Went to go see the crash site where Kobe died, it's so messed up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Had an amazing time at this sex club I go to.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had to get some money from the ATM at the bank.</Answer>
        <Answer>I relaxed at the beach for most of the day.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was at the Hospital because mym friends wife had a baby.</Answer>
        <Answer>My friend got me a full day at the spa.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Any reason you're so nervous right now?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>This is just not the usual for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I always get freaked out talking to cops, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I always fear I have a warrant I don't know about.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is humiliating because people are watching.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm hoping to god this don't end up on YouTube.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh trust me I have my reasons.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ha, If you only knew.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just nervous being stopped that's all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can never remember if all my info is up to date.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not a perfect person and earlier I did some stuff.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I am sorry you think that I am.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just have someone to meet and she's not very understanding.</Answer>
        <Answer>I might have drank some earlier.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't remember if I left my weapon at home or not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who said anything about me being nervous.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh just hoping for no surprise warrants.</Answer>
        <Answer>You cops just make me nervous that's all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I never get in trouble.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you have anything illegal in the vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ha! Like I would tell you.</Answer>
        <Answer>You won't see me incriminating myself haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>*remains silent*</Answer>
        <Answer>I am fully aware of my rights so that won't work on me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will remain silent here if you don't mind.</Answer>
        <Answer>The only search you are getting is an air sniff with the K9.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep Live PD has taught me not to answer that one.</Answer>
        <Answer>In Oregon they can't ask those questions any more.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is this entrapment? It sure feels like it.</Answer>
        <Answer>You pigs are just too funny.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uhhh nah.</Answer>
        <Answer>I let people borrow it all the time so I sure hope not.</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*</Answer>
        <Answer>Next question please.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I most certainly do not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe, but you need more than that for a search.</Answer>
        <Answer>My property is my own business.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am hoping not.</Answer>
        <Answer>The way my kids borrow my car ya never know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dunno.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope and I do not consent to a search either.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's only illegal if you find it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I suggest you call a K9 if you want to know.</Answer>
        <Answer>No officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really, you think I am just going to tell you?</Answer>
        <Answer>That is a big negative.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe but once again I do not consent to a search.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That is for me to know and you not to find out.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Why are you refusing to give me your ID?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Here's the thing I cant, My license is suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shit, I remembered it's suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here's the thing I cant, My license is suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shit, I remembered it's suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*</Answer>
        <Answer>I ... may be suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>They don't give it to me if I'm suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm still suspended that's why.</Answer>
        <Answer>I need to know why you stopped me RIGHT NOW.</Answer>
        <Answer>See funny story... I had my license suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is it possible to get a ticket for a suspended license?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd love to give you it but I'm suspended right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Before you check, I have a suspended license.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so screwed... I am suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a sovereign citizen! (Use SJW menu).</Answer>
        <Answer>dsDon't get upset but I might have a suspended license.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hypothetically speaking what happens if I'm suspended?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to jail, just take me now.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew I should not have drove suspended today.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks scared*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't give you what I don't have.</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost it and don't know where it is at.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was scared because my license is suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Cries*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please I can't go to jail, please call me a taxi.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Introductions Actions~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Your license, registration, and proof of insurance.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, Yeah, one second.</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't be stalking me now because you know my address.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think I got that for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>What is your probable cause again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that really necessary?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, It's around here some place.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure I got all three.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here you go officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I must say it is nice to deal with a nice cop for once.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope I have everything in the glove box.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't remember if I put the updated documents in here.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Rolls eyes at you*</Answer>
        <Answer>I think the bouncer at the club kept it, wait here it is.</Answer>
        <Answer>I may have left it in my other shirt.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope I didn't leave it at the grocery store.</Answer>
        <Answer>Make sure I get that back okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess it's within your legal rights to ask for my ID huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>One moment please, I'll grab that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess that is a valid request.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're a very nice cop.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to slowly reach for it, dont shoot okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you single at the moment?</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright I think I got those.</Answer>
        <Answer>After the club last night I hope I got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is this LivePD? I really hope not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, hold your horses already.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're awfully demanding..I like that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I should have all that right here.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really? Ughhhhh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't you just run my plate?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah if I can find it in this mess.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew you would ask.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are awfully demanding.. that's hot.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here comes the harassment!</Answer>
        <Answer>Not a problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep give me a minute.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Passenger(s) can I see some ID from you?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Nah</Answer>
        <Answer>This is their traffic stop officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>This don't concern me does it?</Answer>
        <Answer>I graciously and LEGALLY decline.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hands Id*</Answer>
        <Answer>They're the one you pulled over, not me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trying to do some fishing on me huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you need mine?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, I got nothing to hide.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is their business please leave me out of it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd rather not.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>My seat belt is on, I committed no crime so NO ID from me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I respect your office and badge but No.</Answer>
        <Answer>Legally unless I committed a crime I don't have to ID myself.</Answer>
        <Answer>According to 46.61.020. only the driver must provide ID on a stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Under what legal grounds of suspicion?</Answer>
        <Answer>No probable cause has been presented to me... so I decline.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Does your passenger(s) need medical assistance?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yeah they're badly hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>What do you think?</Answer>
        <Answer>Can you give them CPR?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, Immediatley.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, they look unconscious.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are they going to be okay, they look hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>They haven't moved.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, they look dead.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope they dont die!</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you know CPR?.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dunno.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so scared right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you think they're dead?</Answer>
        <Answer>We were in an accident and they were hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think that will help.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Introduction Endings~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Just hang out right here for me okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Dont mind me I'll be snap-chatting.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll just catch up on some youtube.</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance you have a time frame?</Answer>
        <Answer>If I see another unit should I just take off? I'm kidding</Answer>
        <Answer>Not like I'm starving anyway or need to eat soon. </Answer>
        <Answer>I will be here waiting.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure hope everything comes back clear.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure what else I would do.</Answer>
        <Answer>Im just gonna tweet your department about you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that for ya.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Fiddles fingers*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll just relax and get comfortable.</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't leave me too long I get bored quick.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I come sit in the front seat like they do in Oaklahoma?</Answer>
        <Answer>I would love to get out and have a smoke.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Taps the steering wheel*</Answer>
        <Answer>Will you still be cool if I have a warrant?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you mind if I turn on some tunes?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be answering some emails on my phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I see another unit should I call my lawyer?</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure what else I would do.</Answer>
        <Answer>It would be my pleasure officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sounds like a plan.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure what else I would do.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whatever happens remember I showed you respect.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not my first rodeo, I know what to do.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll just be here patiently waiting.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I atleast play with your handcuffs?</Answer>
        <Answer>If I have a warrant can we talk about it first?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm live streaming this whole thing so you know.</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it!</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I check my phone or no?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll just be on my phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>Take as long as ya need.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have to piss so please hurry?</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh i know the drill.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Go ahead and Turn off the engine for me please.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>O..O..Okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm well?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hums* What you gonna do when they come for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wait.. what seems to be the trouble?</Answer>
        <Answer>This aint good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Remember you promised to stay cool.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>Remember I'm innocent until proven guitly.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure why buy okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Should I call my attorney first?</Answer>
        <Answer>Had this happen before and it was not good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Everything okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ha!Nothing about this will be fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here we go!</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm getting hooked huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is everything okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is everything aight?</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I do something wrong or?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes Officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't say I didn't see this coming.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do me a favor and step out the vehicle for me.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>O..O..Okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm well?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm comfortable right here though.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hums* What you gonna do when they come for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wait.. what seems to be the trouble?</Answer>
        <Answer>This aint good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Remember you promised to stay cool.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>Remember I'm innocent until proven guitly.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure why buy okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Should I call my attorney first?</Answer>
        <Answer>Had this happen before and it was not good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Everything okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ha!Nothing about this will be fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here we go!</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm getting hooked huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is everything okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is everything aight?</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I do something wrong or?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes Officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't say I didn't see this coming.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: SEAT BELT CHECK">

    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~b~[DRIVER]-SEAT BELT OBSERVATION (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver isn't wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's properly wearing their belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing their seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver has their seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is fastened securely*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is properly wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is half fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing their seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver has their seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is fastened securely*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is properly wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is properly worn*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver has no seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's seat belt is fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's properly wearing their belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Driver's properly wearing their belt*</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~b~[PASSENGER X1] SEAT BELT OBSERVATION (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is half wearing the seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger quickly put on seat belt as you approached.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is seat belt is secure</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly seat belted.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is secure.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger isn't wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing their seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger has their seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is fastened securely*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is half fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is properly worn*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger has no seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly wearing their belt*</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~b~[PASSENGER X2-4] SEAT BELT OBSERVATION (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger has their seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is fastened securely*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger has no seat belt on*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is half wearing the seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is half wearing the seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger quickly put on seat belt as you approached.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is seat belt is secure</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly seat belted.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is secure.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is half fastened*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is properly worn*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger isn't wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing their seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is safely seat belted*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is wearing a seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly wearing their belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger quickly put on seat belt as you approached.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is seat belt is secure</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger is properly seat belted.*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Passenger's seat belt is secure.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~[DRIV]~s~ I notice you're not wearing your seat belt?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ugghh.. honest mistake, I always have it on.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just not a seat belt kind of person.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, I hate that thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh wow, I had no idea.</Answer>
        <Answer>I been getting in and out all day, I forgot it this time.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm always forgetting that thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoops.. click-it or ticket right? Hahaha</Answer>
        <Answer>Sometimes I do forget it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh No! I usually always buckle up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Go figure the one time I forget it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~b~[PASS]~s~ Why are you not wearing your seat belt?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I needed to grab something that fell real fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone fell and I was leaning down to grab it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't usually wear it, it feels like I'm being squeezed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm.. I completely forgot.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's not my thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>We're driving like 5mph.. come on!</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm always forgetting that thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoops.. click it or ticket right? Hahaha</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmm, I'm not the driver though.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't usually drive so I'm not sure of the law.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~b~[PASS]~s~ I'll need your identification okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Seriously!</Answer>
        <Answer>Come on! over a seatbelt?</Answer>
        <Answer>I got it for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, sure thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whatever.. here!</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a bit harsh don't you think.</Answer>
        <Answer>They get the ticket though right? Hahaha</Answer>
        <Answer>Please don't give me a ticket.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Seat belts can't save you if they're only half worn.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm fully aware of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you, I'll wear it from now on.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be more careful.</Answer>
        <Answer>I agree.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's not my thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're absolutley right.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, okay, I get it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>It's the law and I also don't want you to get hurt.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm fully aware of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you, I'll wear it from now on.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe you'll just educate me with a warning?</Answer>
        <Answer>I wouldn't want to get hurt either.</Answer>
        <Answer>I appreciate your concern for me but I'm an adult.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're absolutley right.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, okay, I get it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, I don't want that either.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good looking out officer seriously.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was definatley a mistake.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: MOVING VIOLATIONS">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm stopping you for multiple reasons.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Is my brake light acting up again?</Answer>
        <Answer>I bet I know what one is.</Answer>
        <Answer>I do'nt like the sound of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>As you can see I didnt do well in driving school.</Answer>
        <Answer>I actually thought I was doing pretty good.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm listening.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm dying to know officer, what are they.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope one reason is that im too fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>What on earth did I do?</Answer>
        <Answer>Let's hear your list, go ahead.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a feeling this is list is going to grow.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear this day can't get any worse.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm pretty sure I know a few of them.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're a money hungry pig, so that sounds about right.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really need to pay more attention huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Usually, I only get stopped for one.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Rolls Eyes*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so upset right now!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] Driving at reckless speeds +25MPH.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>My heavens I been meaning to get my gague fixed.</Answer>
        <Answer>WOW.. I did not realize I was going that fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure?</Answer>
        <Answer>In honor of Kobe I was going 24 over.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure? my speedometer must be broken.</Answer>
        <Answer>You guys do it all the time, I just wanted to try it once.</Answer>
        <Answer>Come on I have to piss like a race horse.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not sure what to say, I didn't realize it.</Answer>
        <Answer>My apologies it is a new car.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had full control, in no way was I reckless!</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmm that's a pretty big ticket huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I had a gas station burrito with an immodium AD haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Only reason you stopped me is because I let you.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] Clocked you going +10-15MPH over the limit</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I heard the limit is just a suggestion though?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks nervous and guilty*</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh that was all? phew.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was on my way to Disney plus and thrust.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tell me something I don't know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe I was going that fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm late for school officer, can we speed this up sir.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm in a hurry.. I need to pee.</Answer>
        <Answer>What is the limit around here?</Answer>
        <Answer>Such a smooth ride that you don't realize how fast your going.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry officer my mind was somewhere else.</Answer>
        <Answer>Family emergency... but I will keep it slowed down.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hahaha that's my usual speed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoever makes the speed limit needs to raise it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good job that's what I seen on the speedometer too.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, after I was five over it was easy to go more.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah and I know I am at a stand-still because of you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I never go over that much.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nice try, I was not going that fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think you clocked the other car and thought it was me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just lost my job today, I think im allowed to go ten over.</Answer>
        <Answer>Guilty as charged officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone said their was available singles in my area!</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm really sorry, I am late to a wedding.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I make you laugh can I catch a break?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm OCD and wanted an even number of citations for my insurance.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoever makes the speed limit needs to raise it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nobody knows how to drive in the state!</Answer>
        <Answer>That really is a shame I got caught.</Answer>
        <Answer>Rich people like myself have Auto Pilot, sadly it malfunctioned.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was fiddling with the cruise control and it got stuck.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm, I thought it was a little over but not that much.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] Any reason why you're going so fast?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I wasn't paying attention if I'm going to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was actually being followed and it scared me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just got this thing a tune up and she takes off, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Kinda felt like it.</Answer>
        <Answer>People are just going too slow.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was racing another car back there.</Answer>
        <Answer>I always speed.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I actually dont have a reason. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoops.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had to get to the hospital for an emergency.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I see you guys speeding all the time so i thought i could </Answer>
        <Answer>I'm trying to meet my date at the movies.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really didn't want to be late for the movies.</Answer>
        <Answer>My work called me in to cover an emergency shift. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I never had a dry roast and I didn't want to have one tonight.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good job that's what I seen on the speedometer too.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, after I was five over it was easy to go more.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't have a really good reason, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>If no one has used the roast in the oven that is my excuse.</Answer>
        <Answer>My churches bible study went too late and now I'm in a hurry.</Answer>
        <Answer>My kid freaked out at school and needs me to come get them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trying to get my food home before it gets cold.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ugghh, what's an excuse you haven't heard?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be honest it is just fun to go fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Every now and then I like to test the response of the police.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not that I can think of.</Answer>
        <Answer>That pig cheated on me and I'm going to tell them off!</Answer>
        <Answer>I am OCD and wanted an even number of citations for my insurance.</Answer>
        <Answer>Everyone was speeding HOW DID YOU JUST PICK ME?</Answer>
        <Answer>I wanted to see if "Nine and your mine" was true. It is</Answer>
        <Answer>My life has been so boring I just wanted some excitement.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was late to my son's graduation.</Answer>
        <Answer>The weed store is having a clearance sale!</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I went over the limit but shouldn't you be catching drunks?</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you obviously think I didn't know I would get caught?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just so lonely and need someone to talk to.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do you care? You don't want to hear another excuse.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] You were impeding/obstructing traffic.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>And that is a problem why?</Answer>
        <Answer>The damn check engine light is on.</Answer>
        <Answer>Funny story I forgot to get gas, so I'm almost out.</Answer>
        <Answer>I like making the other drivers go around me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was on tinder swiping a very important match.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was trying to talk to YouTube on my stream.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't know I could get stopped for not speeding.</Answer>
        <Answer>So you want me to speed?</Answer>
        <Answer>I witnessed a wreck last week, I'm still shaken.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am trying to follow google maps and lost signal.</Answer>
        <Answer>I happen to be lost.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was unsure of the speed limit.</Answer>
        <Answer>I that really a law? It sounds made up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I was going slower than I should have but come on!</Answer>
        <Answer>So you stopped me for going too slow??</Answer>
        <Answer>Occasionally I like to piss off people in traffic .</Answer>
        <Answer>Well this did not go the way that I thought it would.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dropped something and was trying to dig under the seat.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't really get a ticket for going too slow can I?</Answer>
        <Answer>Traffic knew to go around me, or atleast they should.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was making sure everyone was going a safe speed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Everyone is a speed demon...I drive safe thank you very much!</Answer>
        <Answer>I was actually doing your job, keeping the people from speeding.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you see how fast some of these hoodlums are driving?</Answer>
        <Answer>You must really have it out for me huh?.</Answer>
        <Answer>Someone did it to me earlier so it was PAYBACK!</Answer>
        <Answer>How about the people who sit at a green light on their phones?</Answer>
        <Answer>I still don't see how what I did is unlawful.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is my fault I am sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I got lost and I freaked out a little bit.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[RED] Did you not see that RED LIGHT back there?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's only split seconds.. it should be fine..</Answer>
        <Answer>The light was yellow, you should check your eyesight!</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I had just beat it. I guess not</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't paying attention if Im going to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>Looked Yellow to me as I went under.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why don't I get praised for the lights I DO stop at?</Answer>
        <Answer>Uhhh yeah.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Gives you puppy dog eyes*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm in a hurry.. I need to pee</Answer>
        <Answer>I did not think I could safely brake in time.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am late for work officer, can we speed this up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm in a hurry.. I need to pee.</Answer>
        <Answer>Those food truck tacos went right through me if you know what I mean.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did not have time to stop for that thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep those suckers back there still waiting hehe.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought it was still yellow.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh-oh big bad me is gonna have a criminal record for a red light.</Answer>
        <Answer>Great I get the one color blind cop, it was YELLOW!</Answer>
        <Answer>I goofed, I know I should have stopped.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I seen it and said to myself ...YOU CAN DO IT!.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really the one time I run a red light and I get stopped?</Answer>
        <Answer>That is a tricky light, I didn't time it correctly.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh woe is me I ran a redlight!... just give the ticket pig.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks concerned*</Answer>
        <Answer>Wow I can't believe I did not see it at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did not, some how I didn't see the light there.</Answer>
        <Answer>Huh that explains why everyone else stopped.</Answer>
        <Answer>In honor of the Black Mamba I'm only stopping at yellows.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[RED] You blew right through that RED LIGHT!</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yep and I'm still going to be late.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think much worse crime is happening to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>I drove I didnt technically blow through it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake sorry officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I went to change my radio and didnt see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>The Vanilla Unicorn is doing 1/2 off titty dances officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I took the cutest selfie *shows you phone*</Answer>
        <Answer>Not this again.</Answer>
        <Answer>Coronavirus is killing people and you're worried about a red light?</Answer>
        <Answer>You're right, I didn't mean to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't you just let me have this one?</Answer>
        <Answer>Lets not go making this a big scene.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm late for school officer, can we speed this up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Someone was chasing me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear to you that damn thing was Yellow.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure did didn't I ... Like the Flash zoooom zooom.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you seen the new girl at the Vanilla Unicorn you would too!</Answer>
        <Answer>I try to run atleast one everyday to save time.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not stopping at a light when no one is there.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do I have to stop if I'm the only vehicle?</Answer>
        <Answer>I reject that, I cautiously moved through that light.</Answer>
        <Answer>I most certainly did not blow through a red light.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well it is your word against mine, oh and my attorney.</Answer>
        <Answer>My lawyer has gotten every red light ticket thrown out.</Answer>
        <Answer>You stopped my whole day to tell me this?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, it happens ya know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess it must be a slow day for you huh?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[STOP] You didn't stop at that STOP SIGN back there.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>They are like every twenty feet!</Answer>
        <Answer>My apologies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh no did I?</Answer>
        <Answer>Look at that.. I did and nobody died.</Answer>
        <Answer>*sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake sorry officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I went to change my radio and didnt see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>When did they put that in there?</Answer>
        <Answer>I took the cutest selfie *shows you phone*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I always forget to completely stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Cause they are a waste of time.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't paying attention if I'm going to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did roll right through that son of a gun didnt I?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hate stopping for a piece of metal.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah and your point?</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt even see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I stopped for like a million of them already.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was taught if no other cars were around I could go.</Answer>
        <Answer>I slowed down and rolled through.</Answer>
        <Answer>WAIT! I have to stop at a stop sign? Mind is blown officer</Answer>
        <Answer>Well see my car was in autopilot and it doesn't do that. </Answer>
        <Answer>I always make sure no one is there before I run them.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think you should have to stop fully.</Answer>
        <Answer>I forgot you don't count it if you almost stop huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>What can I say I love being a hardened criminal.</Answer>
        <Answer>I looked away for one second and I missed it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hopefully that is not grounds for a citation.</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone distracted me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Cite me haha, A Nigerian prince just sent me 2 Million dollars.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SIGNAL] You failed to signal before making your turn.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Its a new car still trying to figure out the switches.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear i turned it on.</Answer>
        <Answer>I been meaning to get that fixed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't paying attention if Im going to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>*looks around*</Answer>
        <Answer>I forgot that was a law.</Answer>
        <Answer>I watch you cops do it all the time, hypocrites much?</Answer>
        <Answer>Someone was chasing me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Driving has so many rules ughhh.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure didn't.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to need to seem some dash cam proof.</Answer>
        <Answer>My mistake.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for saving me from a life of crime officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, gonna have to blame this one on AutoPilot.</Answer>
        <Answer>I actually wasnt sure I wanted to turn before I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>I totally spaced it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I used to drive a BMW so I don't know where it is.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm still getting used to this whole signaling thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think I signaled as I went through, does that count?</Answer>
        <Answer>No one else was around but you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm in the turn lane I think my intent was clear.. TO TURN.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm maybe my bulb is burnt out.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why Me!!</Answer>
        <Answer>I signal for every turn ever yet you catch me this time.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is too much for my anxiety right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks sad*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was confused sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I ended up making the turn last minute, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>How fun, I'm going to jail.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I?</Answer>
        <Answer>You're not pulling my leg are you?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm glad you stopped me so this crime spree can be ended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoops, yeah you caught me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought like only poor people had to do that?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Laughs* oh I thought it was something else.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake sorry officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uggh I am so dissapointed in myself right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am glad you stopped me so you can raise my insurance rates.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just couldn't honk at me, had to pull me over huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Not this again.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SIGNAL] Any reason you didn't signal your turn?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Easy, It's just a turn signal.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think much worse crime is happening to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>So I miss a few here and there.</Answer>
        <Answer>My bluetooth speaker wouldn't connect to my phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost my mind, my teenage daughter told me she's pregnant.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you didn't get me for that it would be something else.</Answer>
        <Answer>These vibrating panties I'm wearing distracted me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not this again.</Answer>
        <Answer>Kobe is dead and you care about me failing to signal a turn?</Answer>
        <Answer>I forgot.</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm fighting off the flu so Im not 100%.</Answer>
        <Answer>Eh.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can make one up.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just making a quick turn thats all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I signaled three other turns but you only care about this one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Umm I didnt feel like it.</Answer>
        <Answer>My family says Im a bad driver.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that an actual law still, havent we evolved as a people?</Answer>
        <Answer>It didn't seem like that big of a deal.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure is a beautiful day out huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Not really</Answer>
        <Answer>Just a force of habit I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>Your uniforms look so sharp, sorry what was that again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Funny when I smoke weed I never forget to signal.</Answer>
        <Answer>When I drink and drive this is never a problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>Once again no one else was around.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake sorry officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>The Auto Pilot of this car is awful.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was not planning to turn and then I needed to.</Answer>
        <Answer>I took the hottest selfie *shows you phone*</Answer>
        <Answer>Instagram has the funnest new filters.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YIELD] You failed to yield to that emergency vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Snarls*</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle is better.</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I had the right of way.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whooptie Dooo.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shouldn't they yield to me?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think that will be on the news but okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry they were on their phone and it pissed me off.</Answer>
        <Answer>They would not make up their mind.</Answer>
        <Answer>I waited and waited.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tracy at the Vanilla Unicorn is working the VIP room.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look I am almost where I need to be, please move this along.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I am sure I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just making a quick turn thats all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was taught if you want something YOU take it.</Answer>
        <Answer>They took too long so I went.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sometimes you have to make people move.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I was pretty aggressive huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't usually drive this way.</Answer>
        <Answer>I recieved some bad news and I am really on edge.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was adjusting the A/C and didn't see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone played an awful song and I had to change it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have it happen to me all the time, but cops are never around.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh no, someone could have gotten hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>I probably should watch more closely.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe they allow me to drive haha.</Answer>
        <Answer></Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YIELD] You failed to yield to another vehicle</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Snarls*</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle is better.</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I had the right of way.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whooptie Dooo.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shouldn't they yield to me?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think that will be on the news but okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry they were on their phone and it pissed me off.</Answer>
        <Answer>They would not make up their mind.</Answer>
        <Answer>I waited and waited.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tracy at the Vanilla Unicorn is working the VIP room.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look I am almost where I need to be, please move this along.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I am sure I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just making a quick turn thats all.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was taught if you want something YOU take it.</Answer>
        <Answer>They took too long so I went.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sometimes you have to make people move.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I was pretty aggressive huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't usually drive this way.</Answer>
        <Answer>I recieved some bad news and I am really on edge.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was adjusting the A/C and didn't see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone played an awful song and I had to change it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have it happen to me all the time, but cops are never around.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh no, someone could have gotten hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>I probably should watch more closely.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe they allow me to drive haha.</Answer>
        <Answer></Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YIELD] Any reason you didn't yield to that pedestrian?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>You would think they would move.</Answer>
        <Answer>They just came out of nowhere.</Answer>
        <Answer>When I am a pedestrian I respect people in a vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not playing games today.</Answer>
        <Answer>My vape ran out of battery mid inhale so I plugged it in.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew if we collided I would be fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>They are the ones who should watch where they are going.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you see how slow they were going?</Answer>
        <Answer>*No comment*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I couldnt tell if they were going or not.</Answer>
        <Answer>They were not obeying traffic sign either.</Answer>
        <Answer>Umm my vehicle is stronger.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did not see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Autopilot is not as smart as they say, I want a refund.</Answer>
        <Answer>Eh.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was looking the other way.</Answer>
        <Answer>A simple finger point from you would have been enough.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I can not think of anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh i just wanted to give them a little scare.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just matched with like 5 hotties of POF.</Answer>
        <Answer>I looked at the oil change sticker and im overdue!</Answer>
        <Answer>I was too busy watching other traffic.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was checking Twitter Im glued to Trump's tweets haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm kind of in a hurry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I shouldnt have to.</Answer>
        <Answer>I waited and then I went, what is the issue?</Answer>
        <Answer>They looked like they might steal my car.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISCELLANEOUS] Following too closely or tailgating.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I was trying to read their bumper stickers sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Was I?</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't believe I was.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wreckon that is not what I happened.</Answer>
        <Answer>What exactly is too close?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sometimes I ride peoples rear ends sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I most certainly was not tailgating.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tailgating is done at a sports arena, do you see one?</Answer>
        <Answer>My welfare check just hit and I had to check my phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hahaha I was hella distracted sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just helping them speed up that's all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you see how hot they were?</Answer>
        <Answer>They cut me off earlier so I wanted to send them a message.</Answer>
        <Answer>Telling them to move their ass!</Answer>
        <Answer>It usually gets people to move over haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was hoping they would move the hell over.</Answer>
        <Answer>I left a car length or two.</Answer>
        <Answer>They were driving SOOO SLOW!</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah and you were no where close at all to see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>They had atleast 1-2 car lengths.. COME ON!</Answer>
        <Answer>People tailgate me all the flipping time, where are you?</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake is all I can say.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am such a reckless driver huh officer?</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe you should arrest me and teach me a lesson.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was reading casual encouters on Craigslist and lost track.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know it's a miracle I don't have their paint on my bumper.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISC] Unsafe lane change/Improper Passing.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ohhh I didn't think any cops were around.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake.</Answer>
        <Answer>Unsafe to you I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, I'll play along.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was really hoping you didn't see that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew you were eyeing me after I did it.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was so stupid of me wasn't it?</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost my cool with them I'll admit that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't know what came over me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not this...</Answer>
        <Answer>They were going way too slow.</Answer>
        <Answer>What was improper about it?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can see how that would alert you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I see... yep you are right.</Answer>
        <Answer>In that moment I just needed to get in that lane.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hahaha I assure you I'm not impaired.</Answer>
        <Answer>My AutoPilot just took over the vehicle and did it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I should pay more attention.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was just day dreaming I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm pretty sure that lady was putting on lipstick.</Answer>
        <Answer>I needed to get over.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was going to miss my turn sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm pretty sure that woman was taking a selfie.</Answer>
        <Answer>I needed into that lane.</Answer>
        <Answer>I panicked I would miss my street.</Answer>
        <Answer>The GPS gave me instructions too late. .</Answer>
        <Answer>Traffic is just a bitch today.</Answer>
        <Answer>What was unsafe about it?</Answer>
        <Answer>Again who got hurt hmm?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISC] Failure to maintain your lane a moment ago.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I spilt a cold drink in my lap. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake.</Answer>
        <Answer>My steering wheel was incredibly hot.</Answer>
        <Answer>I might have been on my phone but if you can't prove that then...</Answer>
        <Answer>You made me nervous driving behind me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn your right.</Answer>
        <Answer>I felt like I was driving okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep and I'm still okay and no one's hurt.</Answer>
        <Answer>I spilt a hot drink in my lap. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>These vibrating panties I'm wearing distracted me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think much worse crime is happening to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have been driving for quite some time I just got tired.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake sorry officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I went to change my radio and didnt see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Bae just sexted me a hot pic *shows you phone*</Answer>
        <Answer>I took the cutest selfie *shows you phone*</Answer>
        <Answer>Failure to what?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISC] Distracted driving or use of a mobile phone.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I wasnt using my phone I dropped it and picked it up.</Answer>
        <Answer>This was a very important text from my sister.</Answer>
        <Answer>Calm down.. No one's dead</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah that was pretty dangerous.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so addicted I can't put it down.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was messaging this cutie on POF.</Answer>
        <Answer>My video on Life Invader just went VIRAL.. WOOOOO!.</Answer>
        <Answer>Someone hacked my e-harmony account and it notified me.</Answer>
        <Answer>My bestie needed my help picking out shoes for her date.</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle don't have GPS so I have to use the phone.</Answer>
        <Answer>I need to stop taking driving selfies huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I usually hold me phone up at the wheel so I can see.</Answer>
        <Answer>I haven't been able to figure out the bluetooth in this vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>Driving is boring and I like to talk while I drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>I run my business out of my car.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISC] Driving reckless or careless/Cutting off a motorist.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I was running late for work officer, it wont happen again!</Answer>
        <Answer>I pay taxes and all of this road is MINE.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is MY road and i will drive on it how I see fit.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I can't believe I did that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Calm your horses please.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was having some fun but I guess that's not allowed.</Answer>
        <Answer>What was reckless?</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest mistake. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>You need to go ticket them too.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear I did not see them until it was too late.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt start it they cut me off first.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew exactly what I was doing though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nobody got hurt so why are you busting my balls?</Answer>
        <Answer>That ass clown shouldnt be driving if you ask me.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[MISC] Burnout/Excessive acceleration.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Just got some new rubber on this bad boy!</Answer>
        <Answer>That other car thought it could take me pffft.</Answer>
        <Answer>From time to time I like people to look at me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just do it to boost my ego.</Answer>
        <Answer>haha I am kind of a jerk that's why.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did see you smoke? Nope.. it wasn't a burnout.</Answer>
        <Answer>So I can only do that in a parking lot?</Answer>
        <Answer>Calm down it is a little smoke and noise.</Answer>
        <Answer>I only did it for a few seconds.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am so sorry I didn't see you there.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will not do that again.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really didn't know that was unlawful.</Answer>
        <Answer>I love hearing my tires squeal.</Answer>
        <Answer>These tires have seen better days so... I burned out.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZARD] You were going too fast for conditions</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I know how to drive okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>You are absoloutley right, my fault officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am in a hurry but I can slow down.</Answer>
        <Answer>How am I supposed to know what is too fast?</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that really a law?</Answer>
        <Answer>I want to make it home before it gets worse.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will keep it slowed down.</Answer>
        <Answer>The roads are little danagerous thats all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah this weather is pretty bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm late for an appointment</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZ] You can not drive at that speed in the SNOW.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>This baby has all wheel drive so YES i can.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh pish posh I know how to drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt think I was going that fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Says who?</Answer>
        <Answer>What is the use of having snow tires then?</Answer>
        <Answer>I was going a bit fast huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am under the speed limit though COME ON!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZ] The roads are too slick to be driving like that.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I know, I know, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>Everyone else is driving fast so I thought I should.</Answer>
        <Answer>They dont seem that slick to me.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZ] You were driving with no headlights.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Honest mistake.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really didnt notice.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I guess your right.</Answer>
        <Answer>My son must have turned off the auto setting.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'm a student driver</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZ] You hit a vehicle/caused an accident.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>What, when?</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think so.</Answer>
        <Answer>As I remember they hit me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I could not stop.</Answer>
        <Answer>Didnt you see them cut me off?</Answer>
        <Answer>I was trying to avoid an animal</Answer>
        <Answer>I could'nt get past them</Answer>
        <Answer>They would'nt let me pass</Answer>
        <Answer>haha I'm kind of a jerk that's why.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohhhh no.</Answer>
        <Answer>One of these days I knew I would do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>My psychic told me this would happen.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are they okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't afford to get sued.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was a fender bender at best.</Answer>
        <Answer>It all happened so quickly.?</Answer>
        <Answer>All I know was we collided.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah you are telling me, this is going to cost a fortune.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[HAZ] Violations for VEHICLE EQUIPMENT-</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Go to VEHICLE VIOLATION MENU</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[CHILL] Any reason why you were littering just now?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>The wind will take care of it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Seriously you are mad about some trash?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure you have littered before, come on.</Answer>
        <Answer>I pay taxes that pay people to clean it up.</Answer>
        <Answer>My window was open and it just flew out.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry my car is a mess and I wanted to clean it out.</Answer>
        <Answer>haha I am kind of a jerk that's why.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's for all the tree hugging hippies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just a stupid decision</Answer>
        <Answer>I wish I could take it back.</Answer>
        <Answer>That trash had old Taco Bell and smelled so bad.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: BACKGROUND">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRI-DUI] You've been arrested for DUI before.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I sure have.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shit it feels just like it was yesterday.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dont remember that at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Addiction is one hell of a beast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I vowed never to do that again.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep they should tell you thats the prize you win.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRIORS-SUS] You've been arrested for driving suspended/revoked.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I had a job and I had to go to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really didnt think anything of it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah it was stupid.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't just stop driving because the court wants me to.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uber is too expensive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thats not me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure you have the right person?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's not good huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>*looks around*</Answer>
        <Answer>That I do.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I learned my lesson though.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRIOR-LICS] You've been cited for an expired license before.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I live paycheck to paycheck, I got no money.</Answer>
        <Answer>I always forget about it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who remembers that anyway?</Answer>
        <Answer>So.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRI-INS] You've been cited for no insurance before.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I only do insurance for 6 months out the year.</Answer>
        <Answer>Insurance is too damn high.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep and I got screwed.</Answer>
        <Answer>A big mistake I know officer.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRI-REG] You've been cited for expired reg before.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I guess.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha more than a few times.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yepppp.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dont like giving money for a damn sticker to put on my plate.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PAR] Why didn't you tell me you were on parole.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Not something I brag about officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>My Thats news to me too.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trying to leave the past in the past.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not something that concerns you.</Answer>
        <Answer>*looks around*</Answer>
        <Answer>I just dont want to go back.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PRO] It looks like you are still on probation?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Going to be for quite some time.</Answer>
        <Answer>They just want to make money off me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Id rather be on probation than in that hell whole.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wow a cop that can read.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[P.O] Can you tell me the name of your P.O.?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Brandyn Brown.</Answer>
        <Answer>Officer Samantha Miller.</Answer>
        <Answer>Jason Gillatt.</Answer>
        <Answer>Kenneth Culpo</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't remember off hand.</Answer>
        <Answer>It just changed this week so I don't know.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ryan Edwards.</Answer>
        <Answer>Rose Alvarez.</Answer>
        <Answer>Mark Hillsong.</Answer>
        <Answer>Carlos Gonzales.</Answer>
        <Answer>Tim Brady</Answer>
        <Answer>Det. Clark Kent</Answer>
        <Answer>I believe it is Trevor Phillips.</Answer>
        <Answer>Jamal Johnson.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[WAR] Were you aware of your warrant for ____?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Fuck!</Answer>
        <Answer>I went to the station last month and they said i didnt have one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well wait, hold on.</Answer>
        <Answer>For what again?</Answer>
        <Answer>When was this?</Answer>
        <Answer>I had it dismissed months ago, Im going to kill that judge.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha Yeah I forgot about that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, I am aware of it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Step out and walk to the back of my cruiser for me.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Haha I am leaving in my car though right?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope you know who you are talking to.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is the last thing I wanted to hear.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I can do that for you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you have any idea how embarassing that will be?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure!</Answer>
        <Answer>My record is squeaky clean just so you know.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: DOCUMENTATION">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~DRIVERS LICENSE~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ask the ped about their drivers license.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[EX-D.L.] Did you know your driver license has expired?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I must have forgotten to renew it. Sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>How does it expire it's a piece of plastic, do I recycle it?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll get to the DMV when I can.</Answer>
        <Answer>With covid it's been a nightmare to get to the DMV.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know it. But I like this license because I look young in the photo.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just give me warning. I'll renew it right away</Answer>
        <Answer>My record is three years without renewing it.</Answer>
        <Answer>It Just expired so I can still drive on it right?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm pretty sure it's lost in all the backed up mail.</Answer>
        <Answer>I rarely drive so I don't renew it often.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[EX-D.L.] Your license is expired past 30 days.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I just have a very hectic life.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I'm not sure how to renew it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll get to the DMV when I can.</Answer>
        <Answer>They stopped sending me notices so I thought it was okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I really have to keep updating that?</Answer>
        <Answer>I been meaning to renew that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I figured I would save the money.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did not want to renew it until I got stopped.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO-D.L] Why are you driving without having a license?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Uh oh..my roommate took the wrong wallet today.</Answer>
        <Answer>I tried to get the license but always failed the tests.</Answer>
        <Answer>They revoked my license a year ago.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just left it at home, I can give you my name.</Answer>
        <Answer>If Illegals can do it why can't I?</Answer>
        <Answer>The odds are very slim I would get stopped.</Answer>
        <Answer>Anyone will tell you I am a good driver.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just drive very safe and I am fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost it.</Answer>
        <Answer>My wallet was stolen from my gym locker.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm still waiting to get it replaced.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SUS-D.L.]Why are you driving with a suspended license?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sorry, I really need to drive to go to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure? They said my license is no longer suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear, I didn't know that my license is suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, that seems very unfortunate huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I have no one to give me rides, I have to use my vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was told they would change it in the system to valid.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought the judge re-instated it, that's what my lawyer said.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't think I would get caught.</Answer>
        <Answer>Because I have to, what kind of dumb question is that?</Answer>
        <Answer>It was an emergency, I needed to visit the hospital.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't know it was still suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I confess I messed up big time.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please, have a heart and help me out.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[REV-D.L.] Why are you driving while your license is revoked?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sorry, I really need to drive to go to work</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure? They said my license was no longer suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear, I didn't know that my license was suspended.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really needed groceries for my kids today.</Answer>
        <Answer>I pretty much finished the classes so I thought I was good.</Answer>
        <Answer>I learned my lesson.</Answer>
        <Answer>The Vanilla Unicorn has half off lap dances.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was not thinking I would get caught.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had to meet up with someone from Tinder.</Answer>
        <Answer>They can't just tell me not to drive!</Answer>
        <Answer>I just do what I want, I'm sorry if you don't like that.</Answer>
        <Answer>What are the odds I would get stopped?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~REGISTRATION OWNER~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Question the ped about thier registration.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[EX-REG] This vehicle has an expired registration.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I didn't get any mail from DMV about the renewal.</Answer>
        <Answer>My secretary must have forgotten to tell me to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just give me warning. I'll renew it right away.</Answer>
        <Answer>So it was broke down and it just got fixed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I still have insurance so what is the big deal?</Answer>
        <Answer>Registration is just a cash grab by the state.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I did not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh, I'm so sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't realize that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I tried this weekend but it was closed for the Holiday.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm, I thought it renewed automatically.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had no idea.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I'll get that taken care of ASAP.</Answer>
        <Answer>It seems I recorded the wrong date when I had to renew it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Whoops, honest mistake.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[EX-REG] Are you aware that it's expired past 30 days?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Things are difficult right now, my job is too demanding.</Answer>
        <Answer>Has it really been that long, I could've sworn it was only a few days.</Answer>
        <Answer>I renewed it, I specifically remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I'll get on that right away.</Answer>
        <Answer>Has it been that long already?</Answer>
        <Answer>I was not aware.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well why should I have to pay again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, Yeah, I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have like 3 vehicles.. I can't keep up with them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah and..?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[No-REG] I show you have no registration on this vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Really? I Had no clue, they never told me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just bought this vehicle last week.</Answer>
        <Answer>Dammit, I'll get right on that tonight!</Answer>
        <Answer>I assumed the dealership handled all of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't have $80 for a sticker to put on my plate.</Answer>
        <Answer>The fees are insane!</Answer>
        <Answer>I share this with my brother and it was his turn to register it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sold this vehicle but I still drive it from time to time.</Answer>
        <Answer>I never do until I get stopped.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not a sucker who pays for a piece of paper.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~REGISTRATION NON-OWNER (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Inform the ped to communicate to the owner.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Let them know the vehicle registration is EXPIRED.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I can't believe they let me drive it with no reg.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm shocked they didn't tell me this.</Answer>
        <Answer>They'll certainly hear about this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll let them know as soon as I see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh you can bet that I will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll do that officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh trust me they will get an earfull from me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes officer.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Let the owner know they need to register this vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I sure will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will be sure to let them know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be sure to inform them.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wish they would have told me this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will do that officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ha! I'm texting them right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh they will be getting an earfull from me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe they didn't register this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be texting them as soon as we're done.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is unacceptable.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's funny that they didn't mention this at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Since it's not my vehicle they get the citation?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'll be citing the owner for the registration today.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>You can give them my traffic violation too haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>That works for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I mean they deserve this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Better them than me.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's fair.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure they're not going to be happy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh they're going to be pissed at me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I bet I get yelled at for this.</Answer>
        <Answer>The owner says they're fine with the citation.</Answer>
        <Answer>That works for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance you could give them a warning?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~INSURANCE OWNER~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ask the ped about their insurance issues.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[EX-INS] Do you know your insurance has expired?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Are you sure? it should be auto-renewed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't have money to renew it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just give me warning. This isn't a ticket I can afford.</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost my job and the funds weren't in the bank.</Answer>
        <Answer>My dad is supposed to take care of all that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure that information is correct?</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure do.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, that's not right.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe, but that don't sound right.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh it was the other vehicle, I got them mixed up.</Answer>
        <Answer>I forgot the little card thingy at home.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO-INS] I show you have no insurance on this vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I didn't know, I guess it got cancelled.</Answer>
        <Answer>Dont need it, I'm an excellent driver!</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just give me warning. I'll renew it right away.</Answer>
        <Answer>Was wondering how the hell you knew about that!</Answer>
        <Answer>I auto pay for that and I thought everything was good.</Answer>
        <Answer>That would be correct, I ain't paying to drive my own vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>I only pay for 6 months out of the year to save money.</Answer>
        <Answer>Those rates are just too damn high?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can barely afford my rent.</Answer>
        <Answer>That does not sound right.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know i updated it last night on the computer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I only pay for 2 months out of the year to save money.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just bought it, so I can't insure it until I have the title.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, I shouldn't be driving it right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>I swear to you that I do.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'll be impounding the vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well doesn't this suck.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll get it taken care of, I promise.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't see why you have to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>All over it not being insured?</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess now I have a new bill to pay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't you just cite me and let me drive it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Would you like me to call you a taxi?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yeah, please.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, since I can't drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you, that would be nice.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sounds good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Screw it, I'll just walk from here.</Answer>
        <Answer>Might as well.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes please.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~INSURANCE NON-OWNER (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Inform the ped to tell the owner.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Let them know the insurance is EXPIRED.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I still have insurance.. so what's the big deal?</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be sure to let them know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe they let me drive it with no insurance.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm shocked they didn't tell me this.</Answer>
        <Answer>They'll certainly hear about this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll let them know as soon as I see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh you can bet that I will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll do that officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh trust me they will get an ear full from me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be sure to inform them.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wish they would have told me this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll do that officer.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Let the owner know they need to insure this vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I sure will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will be sure to let them know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be sure to inform them.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wish they would have told me this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will do that officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ha! I'm texting them right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh they will be getting an earfull from me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe they didn't insure this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be texting them as soon as we're done.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is unacceptable.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's funny that they didn't mention this at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Since it's not my vehicle they get the citation?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'll be citing the owner for the insurance today.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's fair, they didn't insure it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure they're not going to be happy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh they're going to be pissed at me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I bet I get yelled at for this.</Answer>
        <Answer>You can give them my traffic violation too haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>That works for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I mean they deserve this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Better them than me.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's fair.</Answer>
        <Answer>The owner says they're fine with the citation.</Answer>
        <Answer>That works for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance you could give them a warning?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm impounding the vehicle for lack of insurance.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well doesn't this suck.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't want to drive around uninsured.</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand.</Answer>
        <Answer>Watch I get stuck with this impound bill.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't see why you have to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>All over it not being insured?</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess they'llIhave a new bill to pay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't you just cite them and let me drive it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Would you like me to call you an Uber?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yeah, please.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, since I can't drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you, that would be nice.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sounds good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Screw it, I'll just walk from here.</Answer>
        <Answer>Might as well.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes please.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~ALL INFO UNKNOW (COMPULITE) NO REG/INS~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ask the ped the questions below.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>This vehicle comes back with no information at all?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I assure you I do own it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I've had this vehicle for quite sometime.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's strange.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is their anyway you can get the information?</Answer>
        <Answer>I gave you all the paperwork I have.</Answer>
        <Answer>What other way can you find out?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sure you have other ways of finding out.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe a glitch in the systems at the DMV?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Please step out while I collect the VIN and run it.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Umm.. sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh, uh oh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do it.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you think that'll clear this up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmm, I forgot about that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sounds great.</Answer>
        <Answer>That may cause some unforseen issues for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just hurry up.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my vehicle okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>This could be interesting.</Answer>
        <Answer>I should probably make a phone call while you do that.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~y~INVESTIGATE FURTHER AND RUN THE VIN (PRESS)~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Use documentation menu OUTSIDE of vehicle to run vin.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: DUI ALCOHOL">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>We recieved a call you were driving impaired?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well wasn't that thoughtful of them to call me in.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah when I text and drive it can look that way.</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely not!</Answer>
        <Answer>I litterally can't even right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really that's why you stopped me and got me out of my vehicle?</Answer>
        <Answer>Why do people have to ruin everything?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am going to start calling in every little thing I see.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I want to drink and drive that is my business.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well thankfully you have to prove it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really?</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew I should have taken an Uber.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt think I was driving that bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>They don't know good buzzed driving when they see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trust me my sober driving is even worse HAHA.</Answer>
        <Answer>They don't have training, how do they know I'm impaired?</Answer>
        <Answer>Impaired is a funny word isn't it... I-M-Paired haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>It is just all lies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well what happens next?</Answer>
        <Answer>I See people driving impaired all the time, I don't call them in.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am sure this is an honest mistake.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I witnessed you cause an accident just now.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I barely scraped them!</Answer>
        <Answer>It will buff out.</Answer>
        <Answer>They were cool, they wanted that dent.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is ruining my buzz right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle still works fine so...</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle has no damage at all so you're crazy!</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh Ohhh that's not good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Noo, I didnt mean to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think they ran into me, yeah that's what I remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope they are okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry my music was too loud and I didn't see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who was in the accident, I hit a deer or something not a person.</Answer>
        <Answer>HAHAHA oh that is what the huge bang sound was.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I felt something hit my door.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You're having difficulty maintaining your speed.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I was checking fb messenger for crying out loud.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I was doing a pretty good job.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you sure, did you clock me on radar?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah google maps is acting up and told me to turn soon.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry that my driving is not up to your liking.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You do realize you were all ova da woad?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's like Nascar I was warming up the tires thats all.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I wasn't</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I kinda was huh lol?</Answer>
        <Answer>No one else is even out here though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I see the dashcam video or something? </Answer>
        <Answer>I did some have..have some to drink earlier.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sorry, I havent had much sleep.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just really sleepy that is all.</Answer>
        <Answer>This road is bumpy as hell, wheel just jerks side to side.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah okay, show me the dashcam footage.</Answer>
        <Answer>I been driving many years and I can keep a vehicle straight.</Answer>
        <Answer>My friends party was AMAZE-BALLS, so lit right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>uhhh okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is just how I drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I can blame this on AutoPilot I'd like to do so.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry it's my AutoPilot, still kinda glitchy.</Answer>
        <Answer>The alignment is screwed up on this vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>The lanes kept moving sir, I was trying to keep pace with it!</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh did you really?</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't all over the road.</Answer>
        <Answer>I used the two lanes as my own instead of one.</Answer>
        <Answer>I needed extra room because they were driving too close.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I witnessed you cause an accident just now YES.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I barely scraped them!</Answer>
        <Answer>It will buff out.</Answer>
        <Answer>They were cool, they wanted that dent.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is ruining my buzz right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle still works fine so...</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle has no damage at all so you're crazy!</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh Ohhh that's not good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Noo, I didnt mean to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think they ran into me, yeah that's what I remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope they are okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry my music was too loud and I didn't see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who was in the accident, I hit a deer or something not a person.</Answer>
        <Answer>HAHAHA oh that is what the huge bang sound was.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I felt something hit my door.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I notice a strong odor of alcohol on your breath.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>...And what are you trying to say?</Answer>
        <Answer>You really think so?</Answer>
        <Answer>I noticed an odor on your breath too haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>I've never drank the Devil's juice in my life.</Answer>
        <Answer>I drank more than I should have I know?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, that's the Pisswasser.</Answer>
        <Answer>No way! Do you know how long it's been since my last drink?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Struggles to balance*</Answer>
        <Answer>Just alcohol huh? that.. that's good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ughhhhhh, I'm screwed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm of legal age thank you very much.</Answer>
        <Answer>Officer, the party I just came from was SOO LIT!</Answer>
        <Answer>How's it you can smell it and I can't?</Answer>
        <Answer>I do enjoy a good car beer from time to time.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who said you could smell my breath in the first place?</Answer>
        <Answer>I had a few drinks at Tequila-la.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha, I was knocking back shots at the new Diamond Casino.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well what kind of booze have I been drinking then?</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew this was coming.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's been such a long week I needed to relax.</Answer>
        <Answer>So.. I can still operate this motor vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not going to lie that's pretty creepy.</Answer>
        <Answer>I haven't had a drink all week.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>What! I even brushed my teeth too.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew that mouth wash was too strong.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Have you had anything to drink today?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm sorry, I havent had much sleep.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think I may have over done it at the club.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Once I get home I will have a few glasses of wine.</Answer>
        <Answer>None yet.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not sure what day it is today to be honest.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>No that would be irresponsible to drive after drinking.</Answer>
        <Answer>All I drink is Monster energy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Enough to know I can still drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I have.</Answer>
        <Answer>Maybe but I am not going to talk about it.</Answer>
        <Answer>You keep trying to build your case.. it's cute.</Answer>
        <Answer>No.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Seriously when was your last drink?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Like I told you, I haven't been drinking.</Answer>
        <Answer>I threw the can out right before you stopped me.</Answer>
        <Answer>We had a family get together earlier today.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you want the truth or...what?</Answer>
        <Answer>Like I said I have not drank anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>What makes you think I was drinking?.</Answer>
        <Answer>My breath smells like mouthwash not alcohol.</Answer>
        <Answer>I usually have a morning drink.</Answer>
        <Answer>I haven't had a drink.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm always drinking.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know better than to answer that.</Answer>
        <Answer>My last drink was yesterday so I should be fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm insulted you think I would drink and drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.. A few hours ago.</Answer>
        <Answer>A had a drink with my food not even an hour ago.</Answer>
        <Answer>I had a few shots with some friends.</Answer>
        <Answer>Like I said I haven't drank anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>I drank a few glasses of wine on my date.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was partying pretty hard at the beach.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm under the legal limit I assure you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Like I said I have not drank anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you want to know what I ate too? Geeeez.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't see how I'm supposed to remember this.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was earlier today.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just had a liver transplant so I can drink all the time now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Last I checked.. I don't identify as a clock.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you're down we can go have one now?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Licks lips*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, this is a question I'm not anserwing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not answering that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Im thinking I really should have got an uber.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmmm, that is a tough one.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's all a blur to be honest?</Answer>
        <Answer>I threw up a gnarley puddle so I should be good now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Does one really have a last drink?</Answer>
        <Answer>Please don't take me to jail.</Answer>
        <Answer>...Shoot umm bout six hours or so ago.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so sorry, I have a problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>To answer your question I'm usually never sober.</Answer>
        <Answer>It was like an hour ago but I had it with some WhiteCastle.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was actually still drinking it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I forgot my flask at home I usually keep it in the glove box.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd like to buy you a drink for your service.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks around nervously*</Answer>
        <Answer>Well you're the expert, what do you think?</Answer>
        <Answer>I .. I .. dunno I guess a few hours.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>We recieved numerous calls that you were driving impaired?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well wasn't that thoughtful of them to call me in.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well aint that some shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>Seriously numerous calls? My driving is not that bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay whatever.</Answer>
        <Answer>Aww I didn't know so many people cared about me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew someone witnessed me almost hit that mailbox haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I can tell you that is false.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well thankfully you have to prove it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really?</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew I should have taken an Uber.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt think I was driving that bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>They don't know good buzzed driving when they see it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Trust me my sober driving is even worse HAHA.</Answer>
        <Answer>They don't have training, how do they know I'm impaired?</Answer>
        <Answer>Impaired is a funny word isn't it... I-M-Paired haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>It is just all lies.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well what happens next?</Answer>
        <Answer>I See people driving impaired all the time, I don't call them in.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am sure this is an honest mistake.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I observed you swerving everywhere.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm sorry, I havent had much sleep.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just really sleepy that is all.</Answer>
        <Answer>This road is bumpy as hell, wheel just jerks side to side.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah okay, show me the dashcam footage.</Answer>
        <Answer>I been driving many years and I can keep a vehicle straight.</Answer>
        <Answer>My friends party was AMAZE-BALLS, so lit right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>uhhh okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is just how I drive.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I can blame this on AutoPilot I'd like to do so.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry it's my AutoPilot, still kinda glitchy.</Answer>
        <Answer>The alignment is screwed up on this vehicle.</Answer>
        <Answer>The lanes kept moving sir, I was trying to keep pace with it!</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh did you really?</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't all over the road.</Answer>
        <Answer>I used the two lanes as my own instead of one.</Answer>
        <Answer>I needed extra room because they were driving too close.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I witnessed you almost hit someone.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I barely scraped them!</Answer>
        <Answer>It will buff out.</Answer>
        <Answer>They were cool, they wanted that dent.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is ruining my buzz right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle still works fine so...</Answer>
        <Answer>My vehicle has no damage at all so you're crazy!</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh Ohhh that's not good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Noo, I didnt mean to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think they ran into me, yeah that's what I remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope they are okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry my music was too loud and I didn't see them.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who was in the accident, I hit a deer or something not a person.</Answer>
        <Answer>HAHAHA oh that is what the huge bang sound was.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought I felt something hit my door.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Why are you slurring your words?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Fine i wo-wo-wont talk to you then.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is just how i talk.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was testing to you to see if you noticed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Words and thinking is- hard.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am drunk HELLO!</Answer>
        <Answer>I have a disability ... yeah that's it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am buzzed as hell.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's not that bad.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just forget what I am going to say sometimes.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha you said slurring.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am pretty sure my walking won't please you either.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can understand you perfectly fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why..Why..Am I- You slurring your words?</Answer>
        <Answer>I dunno what is with all the questions?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Go ahead and blow into this machine for me.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>I told you I..I.. am not dru-unk.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will but this is a waste of time.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>*takes a deep breath*</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't think I should that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am buzzed as hell.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not admissible in court as evidence of impairment, but okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>You've got to be kidding me.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods nervously*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohh this brings back old memories.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay... Now I'm getting a little worried</Answer>
        <Answer>Umm. Okay</Answer>
        <Answer>I think you need.. a-a- warrant to do this stuff.</Answer>
        <Answer>Set it up and let's do it. I feel lucky.</Answer>
        <Answer>As long as you don't make me do that walk and turn *laughs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Refuses* (Order them out and arrest them)</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright, I will do your stupid test.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I don't have much of a choice do I?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am really starting to doubt my decisions earlier.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do me favor, turn off the engine and step out of the vehicle!</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sure thing officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem, I dont want any issues.</Answer>
        <Answer>As you wish.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is it too late to change my story?</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you serious right now?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm alright.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am so screwed.</Answer>
        <Answer>This happens everytime.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Here we go, tell my kids I love them.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope you got that body cam rolling.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ugggghhh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why does this have to happen?</Answer>
        <Answer>You just want to get a better look at me huh?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: DUI NARCOTICS">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Did you use any drugs today?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I plead the 5th.</Answer>
        <Answer>I been around some people doing it though.</Answer>
        <Answer>I might of hit the bong this morning.</Answer>
        <Answer>Like I am just going to tell you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Get back to why you stopped me in the first place.</Answer>
        <Answer>No way.</Answer>
        <Answer>Drugs are bad, DARE taught me that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just high on life.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just tired. I work 14 hours a day.</Answer>
        <Answer>I honestly cant remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you think I look high or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah my eyes are always red. I think it's normal.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hell no.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not that I remember.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, you wish I would just tell you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can say that I have not.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure wouldn't be driving if I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, but I am buzzing still.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not sure what you are trying to say.</Answer>
        <Answer>My recreational activities are my own business.</Answer>
        <Answer>No.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I haven't.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you have drugs in the vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Honestly, I do not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Honest to God I don't.</Answer>
        <Answer>What is with all these questions?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Gets upset*</Answer>
        <Answer>Not that you can see haha .</Answer>
        <Answer>If I did it's none of your business</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you interrogate everyone like this?</Answer>
        <Answer>I might, I am always lit</Answer>
        <Answer>No but my friends leave that shit in here all the time.</Answer>
        <Answer>No officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure hope not.</Answer>
        <Answer>People are in and out of this thing everyday...so?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not going to answer that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hell to the NAW.</Answer>
        <Answer>No I don't.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods head NO*.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Takes deep breath*</Answer>
        <Answer>I just made the drop, sorry pig.</Answer>
        <Answer>No! is this some kind of a joke?</Answer>
        <Answer>I work 60 hrs a week I dont have time to be high.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why are you harassing me like this?</Answer>
        <Answer>No comment.</Answer>
        <Answer>A meth pipe if anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>If anything a few roaches.</Answer>
        <Answer>I might have a few needles.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I stay away from that stuff.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I notice the odor of narcotics coming from your vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I mean... that is your opinion.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmm I don't.</Answer>
        <Answer>You better be... I paid enough for it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I smoke the best bud in San Andreas!</Answer>
        <Answer>*gulps*</Answer>
        <Answer>You must be tripping, I dont have drugs.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh yeah like what?</Answer>
        <Answer>I mean I did some earlier.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not sure what you are getting at.</Answer>
        <Answer>Like hell you do, thats my momma's casserole.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is some cajun pizza on my breath.</Answer>
        <Answer>I did some earlier and it's on my clothes.</Answer>
        <Answer>I notice you smell really good what cologne is that?</Answer>
        <Answer>You can smell drugs over that nasty breath of yours?</Answer>
        <Answer>My boy buzzard was smoking up in here the other day.</Answer>
        <Answer>I tried some new product down in Davis, just a sampler.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I'm pretty sure you don't.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit for real?</Answer>
        <Answer>That smells good don't it?</Answer>
        <Answer>If you catch a contact I need to charge you some okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am clean as a virgin playing World Of WarCraft.</Answer>
        <Answer>My windows were rolled down like all day, shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks away*</Answer>
        <Answer>Shoot I wish I had the money to get some.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>We recieved numerous calls that you were driving impaired?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well wasn't that thoughtful of them to call me in.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am so sick of people who can't mind their damn business.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you can't tell I am impaired how can they possibly tell?</Answer>
        <Answer>So tired of snitches.</Answer>
        <Answer>What else was your probable cause for this stop?</Answer>
        <Answer>I promise you I am not impaired.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope not a chance.</Answer>
        <Answer>I mean I might be but you have to prove that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Looks like I need to start reporting everyone I see.</Answer>
        <Answer>I ran over the curb a few times a mile back.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hit the curb making a turn awhile ago so sue me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I almost rear-ended a car but I DIDNT because I'm not impaired.</Answer>
        <Answer>Have you ever went for a stoned joyride, shit is amazing?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sometimes I close my eyes to see how long I can go.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You were traveling well under the posted speed limit.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sorry I am not a speed demon like everyone else okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>I like to let life flow and just take everything SLOWWW.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well shit what is the speed limit around here.</Answer>
        <Answer>I go with a speed that I am comortable with.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm this ride is just too smooth I didnt notice.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uhh my pacemaker don't like if I go too fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shouldn't you be out catching speeders?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a little high and I was snapchatting, sorry.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I observed you swerving all over the road.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm sorry sir, I havent had much sleep.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think I may have over done it at the club.</Answer>
        <Answer>The alignment is screwed up on this car.</Answer>
        <Answer>The lanes kept moving sir, I was trying to keep pace with it!</Answer>
        <Answer>Still getting used to this steering.</Answer>
        <Answer>My contact lense moved around on me and I couldn't see.</Answer>
        <Answer>My damn arthirtist flared up in my wrist, sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I moved a few times over the lines... COME ON!</Answer>
        <Answer>I was having some difficulty seeing the lanes.</Answer>
        <Answer>My windshield is dirty and I couldn't see.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[K-9] I have a partner coming with a K9 unit.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Let us hope that he gets in an accident, im joking.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wait... for real?</Answer>
        <Answer>How long does that usually take?</Answer>
        <Answer>If they can't make it I am in the clear?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sounds like fun.</Answer>
        <Answer>3 is a party let's do this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you trying to scare me?</Answer>
        <Answer>I have some NetFlix N Chill happening if we can hurry up.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is not my lucky day is it?</Answer>
        <Answer>Bring it on!</Answer>
        <Answer>Is this standard with all your traffic stops?</Answer>
        <Answer>I have dogs at home so a k9 don't scare me.</Answer>
        <Answer>*sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure it's not like I am in a hurry or anything.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Takes a deep breath*</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[K-9] I am going to run my K9 around the vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>A dog is going to tell you if I have drugs hidden?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can refuse this can't I?</Answer>
        <Answer>This is a violation of my property or something like that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Because you smell a little something you have to do all this?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sniff away fido.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is fine with me.</Answer>
        <Answer>As long as we can hurry this along.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit, you have a K9 with your right now?</Answer>
        <Answer>I might make a phone call while you are doing that.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs and rolls eyes*</Answer>
        <Answer>This is just bullshit.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know all about the air sniff and how it works okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ohhh can I pet it?</Answer>
        <Answer>*laughs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I have nothing to hide so do your thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just got 1k likes on Instagram, do you think I care?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[K-9] My partner is going to run the K9 around the vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ahhh shit I seen this on LivePD the other week.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh yeah, trying to sniff the air around my vehicle right?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I have to stay still or can I move around.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is new to me, a dog that is ia police officer?</Answer>
        <Answer>Seems they give a badge to anyone huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>What's next a drug snniffing cat? Hahaha</Answer>
        <Answer>You should YouTube Feline Unit prank, its hilarious.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do whatever you gotta do cuz.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Seems scared*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks Nervous*</Answer>
        <Answer>I am good they searched this thing at the border last week.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look, I don't want any problems.</Answer>
        <Answer>This should be fun, can't wait to see what happens.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[K-9] The K9 officer did not alert of any narcotics.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I told you! but no you want to waste my time.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn K9 is better trained than you it seems.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is because I am clean, I don't have drugs.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew it wouldn't</Answer>
        <Answer>*Shakes head*</Answer>
        <Answer>That dog just made you look like a rookie.</Answer>
        <Answer>That was really impressive though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Like he was going to smell it through my car?</Answer>
        <Answer>I would have been just as shocked if he would have alerted.</Answer>
        <Answer>With all the people I loan this to I am surprised?</Answer>
        <Answer>Mhhhhmmmm.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just like I said.</Answer>
        <Answer>It has got to be hard for you to trust people huh?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[K-9]The K9 officer alerted of narcotics just now.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well how do I know that is not just a trick you taught it?/</Answer>
        <Answer>Go figure, this is set up.</Answer>
        <Answer>So what does that mean?</Answer>
        <Answer>So what happens next?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sooooo now what?</Answer>
        <Answer>You are going to ask me to step out huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>No shit, that is an amazing dog can I get one?</Answer>
        <Answer>Who's a very very bad doggy?</Answer>
        <Answer>That little shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>He must be smelling my friend, he's always blazin.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I had that dog I would never lose my stash again!</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope I am not buying that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am just as surprised as you are.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Step out of the vehicle for me at this time.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sure thing officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Shit.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem, I dont want any problems.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really?</Answer>
        <Answer>Your wish is my command.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is going to suck.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is not even cool.</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Time for the fun to begin.</Answer>
        <Answer>Stupid, stupid, I am so stupid.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh-oh.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: STOLEN VEHICLE">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you own this vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, I swear to God.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. I don't</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes,Last time I checked the bills came in my name.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I absoulutely do?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, but why is that any of your business.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah. It aint mine.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. I can't afford a ride like this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, got it this week too.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah, not with my credit all jacked up.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I'm just taking it for a spin.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I mean no. ughh!</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, haha it is now.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah, not for very long.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes.(Ask about the shattered glass using [OBSERV])</Answer>
        <Answer>No, but it's all good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, free and clear.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, can you believe someone just let me have it.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, but I knew you was profiling me though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep. She's a sweet ride huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, hot off the show room floor.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. *looks scared*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I think it's a 2021 model.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. (Ask about the exposed wiring using [OBSERV])</Answer>
        <Answer>No, but i'm not worried fam.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I just hope I have all the paperwork.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I don't see why you're always hassling me though.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, not exactly.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. It should be though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep. I've had it for quite awhile.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] How long ago did you buy it?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, its mine, just bought it from this cat down the street</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my moms car, I borrowed it from her to run an errand</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely. Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a funny question to ask, did you run my plates?</Answer>
        <Answer>No sir its my friends vehicle, he let me borrow it for a few hours.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you profiling me officer? That's not gonna look good on your record.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] How much did you buy it for?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, its mine, just bought it from this cat down the street</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my moms car, I borrowed it from her to run an errand</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely. Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a funny question to ask, did you run my plates?</Answer>
        <Answer>No sir its my friends vehicle, he let me borrow it for a few hours.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you profiling me officer? That's not gonna look good on your record.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] Recite the last 3 digits of your license plate.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, its mine, just bought it from this cat down the street</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my moms car, I borrowed it from her to run an errand</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely. Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a funny question to ask, did you run my plates?</Answer>
        <Answer>No sir its my friends vehicle, he let me borrow it for a few hours.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you profiling me officer? That's not gonna look good on your record.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] Why is this vehicle registered to someone else?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, its mine, just bought it from this cat down the street</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my moms car, I borrowed it from her to run an errand</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely. Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a funny question to ask, did you run my plates?</Answer>
        <Answer>No sir its my friends vehicle, he let me borrow it for a few hours.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you profiling me officer? That's not gonna look good on your record.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] Where is the Temporary Registration Tag?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES] Do you have the bill of sale/title?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] Why are you driving this vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] Did the owner give you permission to take the vehicle?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Come on man, I just have a letter from the previous owner passing ownership</Answer>
        <Answer>I just bought this vehicle last week, it hasnt arrived in the mail yet.</Answer>
        <Answer>Right now I am a afraid I cant, I thought the dealership handles that stuff</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I should be carrying that with me at all times huh, I think I left it home.</Answer>
        <Answer>I assumed the dealership handled all that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think this is where I plead the 5th!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] Oh.. and how long ago was that?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] If call them right now they'll say it's okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Come on man, I just have a letter from the previous owner passing ownership</Answer>
        <Answer>I just bought this vehicle last week, it hasnt arrived in the mail yet.</Answer>
        <Answer>Right now I am a afraid I cant, I thought the dealership handles that stuff</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I should be carrying that with me at all times huh, I think I left it home.</Answer>
        <Answer>I assumed the dealership handled all that.</Answer>
        <Answer>I think this is where I plead the 5th!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] Do you know the R.O.'s first name?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes, its mine, just bought it from this cat down the street</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my moms car, I borrowed it from her to run an errand</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely. Why do you ask?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a funny question to ask, did you run my plates?</Answer>
        <Answer>No sir its my friends vehicle, he let me borrow it for a few hours.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you profiling me officer? That's not gonna look good on your record.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[NO] And.. How do you know the owner?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I dunno how that's possible, I just bought it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit! That's crazy! That's impossible man, this is my ride.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why don't you check it in your system?</Answer>
        <Answer>its my parents car</Answer>
        <Answer>I borrowwed it from my friend</Answer>
        <Answer>I just wanted to take it out for a test drive</Answer>
        <Answer>I have the right to remain silent, So I choose to exercise that right!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[OBSERV] Why is their shattered glass on the floor?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It was broken into last week and I haven't cleaned it up.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was in an accident and that is leftover glass from it.</Answer>
        <Answer>What glass?, WOW.. you are observant.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[OBSERV] Tell me about the exposed wires im seeing?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Haha.. my boi never finished putting in the radio.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was trying to re-wire a fuse for the... blinker.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh that? I lost the plastic covering.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[OBSERV] I can see your tools on the floor board.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[OBSERV] Explain the pry marks on the door jam.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[OBSERV] Is that the owners screw driver in the ignition?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>That was it! *snaps fingers* The dude forgot to put it in the vehicle when I bought
          it</Answer>
        <Answer>You know I dont think the dealership gave me one.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn dog ate it and I am actually waiting for the DMV to send me another copy</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Did you steal it? Be honest with me.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I dunno how that's possible, I just bought it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit! That's crazy! That's impossible man, this is my ride.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why don't you check it in your system?</Answer>
        <Answer>its my parents car</Answer>
        <Answer>I borrowwed it from my friend</Answer>
        <Answer>I just wanted to take it out for a test drive</Answer>
        <Answer>I have the right to remain silent, So I choose to exercise that right!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Right now I'm not buying your story.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I dunno how that's possible, I just bought it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit! That's crazy! That's impossible man, this is my ride.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why don't you check it in your system?</Answer>
        <Answer>its my parents car</Answer>
        <Answer>I borrowwed it from my friend</Answer>
        <Answer>I just wanted to take it out for a test drive</Answer>
        <Answer>I have the right to remain silent, So I choose to exercise that right!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>The owner has called and reported it stolen.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I dunno how that's possible, I just bought it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh shit! That's crazy! That's impossible man, this is my ride.</Answer>
        <Answer>Why don't you check it in your system?</Answer>
        <Answer>its my parents car</Answer>
        <Answer>I borrowwed it from my friend</Answer>
        <Answer>I just wanted to take it out for a test drive</Answer>
        <Answer>I have the right to remain silent, So I choose to exercise that right!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Turn it off and come talk to me out here.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sure thing officer, here we go with the bullshit</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem sir, I dont want any problems</Answer>
        <Answer>As you wish bossman</Answer>
        <Answer>Damnit, what seems to be the problem officer?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: VEHICLE EQUIPMENT">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You don't have the required helmet for riding that.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I ride like this all the time.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh, yeah I forgot.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can put it on if you like.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that still a law?</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn't plan on riding just now.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's all good, I just needed to make a quick trip.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know your headlight is broken?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Please forgive me sir, I'll have it fixed by today</Answer>
        <Answer>It's fine. I can still see the road</Answer>
        <Answer>The other one is still working, I suppose</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know your brakelights aren't working?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Please forgive me sir, I'll have it fixed by today</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh sorry, I'm not aware about that</Answer>
        <Answer>It worked before. Must be those stupid mechanics</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I noticed smoke coming from under your hood.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I guess that is why the oil light finally went off haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, I was trying my best to get it to the gas station.</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you know what it could possibly be?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Your vehicle is un-roadworthy at this point.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ohhh that will buff right out hahaha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah a deer jumped out in front of me.</Answer>
        <Answer>She is still purring though come on!</Answer>
        <Answer>I lost control and hit a tree or a kid, im not sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Your telling me this is going to cost a fortune.</Answer>
        <Answer>I destroyed one of those wild boars haha.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know your windshield is broken?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes of course. I need some air</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm about to go to fix it</Answer>
        <Answer>Let's hope it's not raining today</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know that neon/underglow is illegal?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I know. But it looks cool</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry, I don't know about that</Answer>
        <Answer>If you don't like it, I can turn it off</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know your window is broken?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Someone broken into my car last night</Answer>
        <Answer>It got hit by a golf ball yesterday when I passed that golf course</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't know sir. Thanks for letting me know</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you know your window tint is too dark?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's fine. I can see the road from inside</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm too shy, sir</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't want people to look into my car</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Your vehicle does not have a license plate as required.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I am pretty sure someone stole it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I let a friend use it and they never gave it back.</Answer>
        <Answer>I actually just bought this car and dont have the plates yet..sorry.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You are driving without a helmet which is very dangerous.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Ummmm..so its my head not yours.</Answer>
        <Answer>I drive like this all the time no biggie.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have it with me sorry, I'll put it on right now.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Are you aware you are driving with an unsecure load?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I think I made it secure enough</Answer>
        <Answer>At least it doesn't fall off</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sorry, I don't have money to rent a truck</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: COVID ENFORCEMENT">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SAH] A stay at home ordinance is in effect.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm pretty aware of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wait..again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh.</Answer>
        <Answer>What exactly does that mean?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so confused is that different from shelter in place?</Answer>
        <Answer>When did that start again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Ugghhh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah.. I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is getting rediculous.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmmmm really?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks around*</Answer>
        <Answer>Sooo..</Answer>
        <Answer>And?</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that for everyone?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll make this trip quick.</Answer>
        <Answer>Is that so?</Answer>
        <Answer>Say what?</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh not that again.</Answer>
        <Answer>I refuse to do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ummm okay.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know that's crazy huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>What does that have to do with me?</Answer>
        <Answer>Why should I care about that.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is AMERICA!</Answer>
        <Answer>My mistake.</Answer>
        <Answer>I heard.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know. It's all over the news.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll make it fast, don't worry.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SAH/NO] Why are you not at home?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I have no work and I'm bored.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought a good fishing trip would cure my anxiety.</Answer>
        <Answer>I got stuff to do.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought we could leave the house for stuff?</Answer>
        <Answer>Vanilla Unicorn has socially distanced lap dances.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm buying stuff so I can work from home.</Answer>
        <Answer>trust me I want to be at home.</Answer>
        <Answer>Unfortunatley my work is still open.</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn't ready for this work from home stuff.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was going to have a beach day and have it all to myself.</Answer>
        <Answer>I don't have a good answer.</Answer>
        <Answer>What exactly does that mean?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so confused is that different from shelter in place?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so confused is that different from shelter in place?</Answer>
        <Answer>Too many people are at home right now.</Answer>
        <Answer>The kids are driving me insane.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Rolls eyes*</Answer>
        <Answer>(Ask them about violating the stay at home order previously using OBSERVE.)</Answer>
        <Answer>Uggh it's so boring though.</Answer>
        <Answer>My family is on my last nerve. sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I pay insurance on my vehicle and I'm going to drive it.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's so much easier to drive when theirs no traffic.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just had to run out for real fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I love not having all the traffic.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't stay home all day.</Answer>
        <Answer>Last I checked, I'm not on house arrest.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was going to shelter in place at a friends house.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just don't want to be.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have too many errands to run.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can't I be going to essential places or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't go to work so I don't know what to do with myself.</Answer>
        <Answer>My kid wanted a new toy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Theirs nothing fun to do there.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just going to work. </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[YES/NO] Are you an essential worker?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>No, I'm unmeployed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes I am officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>No. I lost my job in this whole thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I am indeed.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I'm concidered essential.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, but I'd rather be home collecting sweet unemployment.</Answer>
        <Answer>Haha No.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I sure am.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, Yep.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I am allowed to work from home.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, my boss still thinks it's a good idea to be open.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah I am.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ugghh No I'm not.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, my work is essential.</Answer>
        <Answer>No.. but I can't be sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, not really.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, and what another lovely day from hell it will be.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, apparently my job isn't valuable to society.</Answer>
        <Answer>No officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I sure am.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, according to the company email I am.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uggh Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmm.. I guess not</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I have to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I wish I wasn't though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes, I'm on the frontlines.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, it sucks though.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, I'm not able to work at the moment</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SAH/NO] Only travel to essential businesses is allowed.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yeah.. that's what I was doing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm aware of that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Those rules make no sense actually.</Answer>
        <Answer>So I can travel but I'm ask not to if I don't need to?</Answer>
        <Answer>Cleary we can see that no law has been broken here</Answer>
        <Answer>Who decides what is essential to my life and needs?</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay, sounds fair.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am just out getting food, I think that's essential.</Answer>
        <Answer>Taking my daily trip to Burgershot.</Answer>
        <Answer>Am I still allowed to go to the park?</Answer>
        <Answer>I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to the grocery store.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm Jjst grabbing a pack of Redwoods.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not paying $20 to doordash for a $5 taco!</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm on essential business to the grocery store.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so sick of this essential travel nonsense.</Answer>
        <Answer>As an adult I think I can decide what is essential to me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did I need a permit or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks nervous*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm spending a few hours at the Vanilla Unicorn for thearapy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Essentially I'm only going to get essentials, see what I did lol?</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Officer I assure you my travel is essential.</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright, I wasn't thinking this would be a big deal.</Answer>
        <Answer>I only wanted to go to see my weed man.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SAH/YES] What do you do for work?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I slave away at the Amazon warehouse.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at the hospital.</Answer>
        <Answer>Down the street at the grocery store.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work the Kluckin Bell drive thru.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'd rather not say, It's embarassing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a cashier.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a CNA.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work road construction.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a contractor, we are allowed to work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a real estate agent.. no a Dr.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at the gas station around the block.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ughhh Burgershot.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a mail carrier.</Answer>
        <Answer>I drive the city buses.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just fix roads.</Answer>
        <Answer>Crane operator down at the shipping yard.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a safety inspector.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at LS International Airport.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a pilot.</Answer>
        <Answer>Cashier at the pet store.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm an officer just like you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a flight attendant.</Answer>
        <Answer>Funny you ask, police dispatcher.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a long haul trucker.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods head* No.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at LSFD.</Answer>
        <Answer>Burgershot.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm an RNA.</Answer>
        <Answer>I manage the LTD a few blocks away.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a firefighter.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you must know I direct a funeral home, I'm needed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just stock the shelves that people strip bare.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am a receptionist at the hospital.</Answer>
        <Answer>A nursing home..</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a desk person at a clinic.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a paramedic.</Answer>
        <Answer>Active military.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm a sanitation worker.</Answer>
        <Answer>Someone has to make sure the trash get's picked up.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work at the post office.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PUB] All restaurants and bars are ordered closed.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I haven't had a decent meal in months.</Answer>
        <Answer>What about us people who are too lazy to cook?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm dying to have my favorite food again.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm tired of drive thru, I want to dine in.</Answer>
        <Answer>Anychance they will be opening again soon?</Answer>
        <Answer>What are these poor owners going to do?</Answer>
        <Answer>How am I supposed to hook up with random strangers?</Answer>
        <Answer>Wait again?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well for how long?</Answer>
        <Answer>I actually didn't know that</Answer>
        <Answer>Well what the hell?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep.</Answer>
        <Answer>We need to vote the governor of San Andreas out.</Answer>
        <Answer>Theaters too! Ugggh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Those poor bar owners.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't say I blame them, cases are spiking like crazy.</Answer>
        <Answer>The liquor stores are still open huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I did.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is horrible timing this weekend.</Answer>
        <Answer>My friend is a bar tender and she's pissed.</Answer>
        <Answer>So I can't bar hop or go clubbing?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am aware, thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh I just planned on drinking at a friends.</Answer>
        <Answer>This virus is messing with my sex life.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm dying to have my favorite food again.</Answer>
        <Answer>I just want to hit the club again.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sadest day of my life is when they closed the Vanilla Unicorn.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't even get black out drunk.</Answer>
        <Answer>Where am I goingn to take my date?</Answer>
        <Answer>Amazing the night life is just gone.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm dying to go dancing at Tequila-la.</Answer>
        <Answer>Bar hopping is a part of who I am!</Answer>
        <Answer>How am i supposed to get black out drunk.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I hope they open soon.</Answer>
        <Answer>All the good places are closed, unbelieveable.</Answer>
        <Answer>Of course they let GMO places like Burgershot stay open.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yeah, I hear ya.</Answer>
        <Answer>All my favorite watering holes just dried up and are gone.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PUB] All public areas remain closed at this time.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>They just shut everything down.</Answer>
        <Answer>So.. I can't even go to the park?</Answer>
        <Answer>I pay taxes so these places can operate!</Answer>
        <Answer>So I've heard.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay.. Okay!</Answer>
        <Answer>And..</Answer>
        <Answer>So no hunting?</Answer>
        <Answer>I go fishing all the time though.</Answer>
        <Answer>No camping in the SA National park?</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a bummer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm already here so..</Answer>
        <Answer>What are we supposed to do.</Answer>
        <Answer>So everything is just like...closed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't even go to the beach today?</Answer>
        <Answer>It's my anniversary today and we were going to the beach.</Answer>
        <Answer>But the weather is so nice for the beach.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't believe this.</Answer>
        <Answer>All of this over a flue!</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay then.</Answer>
        <Answer>I've never seen this in my life before.</Answer>
        <Answer>What a shame.</Answer>
        <Answer>Coronavirus is ruining my life.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know they closed down the MALL!.</Answer>
        <Answer>This is like the worst time to be alive.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are they trying to kill us with boredom?</Answer>
        <Answer>You mean I can't go surfing today?</Answer>
        <Answer>I walk the beach everyday for my exercise.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can they really do that?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I guess I have no choice but to go home.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fine I'll go home.</Answer>
        <Answer>This blows a big greasy one!</Answer>
        <Answer>This is just insane.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's like the whole world has gone crazy.</Answer>
        <Answer>This madness needs to end immediatley.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't exercise at the gym and now I can't swim in the ocean?</Answer>
        <Answer>The ocean is quite big enough to socially distance myself.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I drove all this way.</Answer>
        <Answer>What now?</Answer>
        <Answer>What should I do now?</Answer>
        <Answer>Seriously it's all shut down?</Answer>
        <Answer>What do you suggest?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PUB] Remember A mask is required in all public places..</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sounds lovely.</Answer>
        <Answer>I haven't washed my mask in 2 weeks haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>You mean like everywhere?.</Answer>
        <Answer>When did this happen?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Is quiet*</Answer>
        <Answer>You know you can still smell peoples bad breath?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope this ends soon, i hate masks.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>Even here?</Answer>
        <Answer>Is this state wide or just in the major cities?</Answer>
        <Answer>I got mine in my glovebox.</Answer>
        <Answer>I ain't wearing no mask.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good thing I'm just going to stay in.</Answer>
        <Answer>America home of the free huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Wearing a mask violates my CCW, funny huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>We gotta stop the spread somehow?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope we don't have to wear it on the beaches.</Answer>
        <Answer>They said a mask isnt helpful a few months ago.</Answer>
        <Answer>Crazy this is the new norm huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep i know.</Answer>
        <Answer>Surprised we don't have to wear one in the car.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[PUB] Try to avoid large gatherings if possible.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I'm ready to catch it and get it over with.</Answer>
        <Answer>Don't get me started on that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Understood.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Is quiet*</Answer>
        <Answer>You know it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>The Holidays are all about large gatherings though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Only if I'm going to the grocery store its okay huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I will go to whatever gathering I please.</Answer>
        <Answer>Went to a protest this week and didnt hear a thing.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll do my best.</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand the risks.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's common sense huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I just want to eat some good bbq and get drunk.</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright.</Answer>
        <Answer>Might as well cancel everything!</Answer>
        <Answer>I shouldn't even be here I should be in Hawaii.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: CMV INSPECTION">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Inspection Beginning~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I stoped you today for a rotuine inspection?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>No Problem.</Answer>
        <Answer> Well that's probably not going to end well.</Answer>
        <Answer> WHAT?!? YOU CAN DO THAT! </Answer>
        <Answer> Can you hurry up, I'm running low on hours. </Answer>
        <Answer> Do I have to log this on duty?</Answer>
        <Answer> Well today is my LUCKY day. HAHA </Answer>
        <Answer> Well that sucks. </Answer>
        <Answer> What you couldn't find a SWIFT driver to pick on?</Answer>
        <Answer> Can we do this tomorrow, I'm late for my delivery. </Answer>
        <Answer> Was J.B. Hunt busy,so you decided to ruin my day? </Answer>
        <Answer> Do you do this to automobile drivers too? </Answer>
        <Answer> The cartel wouldn't like that.</Answer>
        <Answer> That's what she said!</Answer>
        <Answer> Alright, what all do you need?</Answer>
        <Answer> Got everything you need, let's get on with it.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You haven't done anything wrong.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Oh thank goodness.</Answer>
        <Answer> Good to know officer.</Answer>
        <Answer> I wasn't paying attention,thought I was speeding.</Answer>
        <Answer> Yeah I know how this works.</Answer>
        <Answer> So why are we here? </Answer>
        <Answer> For a minute I thought you seen me throw that doughnut at you, HAHA!</Answer>
        <Answer> That's what you think.</Answer>
        <Answer> I may have a warrant actually.</Answer>
        <Answer>Damn right.</Answer>
        <Answer> Yeah I know. </Answer>
        <Answer> Hope it stays that way.</Answer>
        <Answer> That's what she said.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Can you open your door, please? </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*opens door* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>

    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Inspection Questions~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Where you coming from?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Picked this up over in Liberty City. </Answer>
        <Answer>Los Santos. </Answer>
        <Answer> Down at the port. </Answer>
        <Answer>Vice City. </Answer>
        <Answer> Paleto Bay. </Answer>
        <Answer> Rockford Hills.</Answer>
        <Answer> Davis.</Answer>
        <Answer> Vinewood.</Answer>
        <Answer> I picked this up in a parking lot on the border.</Answer>
        <Answer> If I were you, I wouldn't worry about it.</Answer>
        <Answer> Mind your own business.</Answer>
        <Answer> Asking questions may get you hurt officer.</Answer>
        <Answer> Not really sure.</Answer>
        <Answer> The old home filler-up and keep on truckin cafe.</Answer>
        <Answer> Mirror Park. </Answer>
        <Answer> Grapeseed.</Answer>
        <Answer> Sandy Shores. </Answer>
        <Answer> Downtown.</Answer>
        <Answer> Harmony. </Answer>
        <Answer> Fort Zancudo.</Answer>
        <Answer> Vespucci. </Answer>
        <Answer> Davis.</Answer>
        <Answer> Los Santos International. </Answer>
        <Answer> Del Perro.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Where You Headed to?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> Cluckin Bell up in Paleto </Answer>
        <Answer>Out to Harmony </Answer>
        <Answer> Sandy Shores</Answer>
        <Answer>Wolf creek pass, way up on the great divide. </Answer>
        <Answer> Pibwasser brewery</Answer>
        <Answer> Chumash </Answer>
        <Answer>Paleto Bay </Answer>
        <Answer>Out around Grapeseed somewhere </Answer>
        <Answer>The truck stop in Paleto </Answer>
        <Answer> The shipping port in Los Santos </Answer>
        <Answer> Liberty City</Answer>
        <Answer> Vice City</Answer>
        <Answer> Probably out of service at this point HAHA </Answer>
        <Answer> Meeting a guy someplace off of 13 down here. </Answer>
        <Answer> Just up route 1 about 100 miles.</Answer>
        <Answer> Hopefully not to JAIL! </Answer>
        <Answer>Well that depends how well this inspection goes. </Answer>
        <Answer> Wherever my GPS tells me to. </Answer>
        <Answer> Down to the airport. </Answer>
        <Answer>None of your business. </Answer>
        <Answer>The cartel won't like you asking that. </Answer>
        <Answer> To meet the ballers on Dutch London street. </Answer>
        <Answer>Davis. </Answer>
        <Answer>JAIL </Answer>
        <Answer> Eastbound and down!</Answer>
        <Answer> Denver. </Answer>
        <Answer> Pueblo. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cleveland. </Answer>
        <Answer> Detroit. </Answer>
        <Answer> Dallas. </Answer>
        <Answer> Houston. </Answer>
        <Answer> San Antonio </Answer>
        <Answer> Fort Worth. </Answer>
        <Answer> Amarillo. </Answer>
        <Answer> Oklahoma City </Answer>
        <Answer> Colorado Springs. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cheyenne. </Answer>
        <Answer> Salt Lake City. </Answer>
        <Answer> Las Vegas </Answer>
        <Answer> Ogden. </Answer>
        <Answer>Portland. </Answer>
        <Answer> Seattle. </Answer>
        <Answer> Boise.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bozeman.</Answer>
        <Answer> Tacoma.</Answer>
        <Answer> Spokane.</Answer>
        <Answer> Fargo. </Answer>
        <Answer> Rapid City.</Answer>
        <Answer> Billings. </Answer>
        <Answer> Albuqueque. </Answer>
        <Answer> Santa Fe. </Answer>
        <Answer> Minneapolis. </Answer>
        <Answer> St. Paul. </Answer>
        <Answer> Wisconsin.</Answer>
        <Answer> Daytona Beach</Answer>
        <Answer>Jacksonville. </Answer>
        <Answer> Lake Charles. </Answer>
        <Answer> New Orleans.</Answer>
        <Answer> Shreveport. </Answer>
        <Answer> Lafayette, LA. </Answer>
        <Answer> Jackson, MS. </Answer>
        <Answer> Gulfport, MS. </Answer>
        <Answer> Biloxi. </Answer>
        <Answer> Texarkana. </Answer>
        <Answer> Little Rock. </Answer>
        <Answer> Pine Bluff, AR. </Answer>
        <Answer> Fort Smith. </Answer>
        <Answer> Jonesboro, AR. </Answer>
        <Answer> West Memphis. </Answer>
        <Answer> Montgomery, AL.</Answer>
        <Answer> Mobile, AL. </Answer>
        <Answer> Birmingham, AL.</Answer>
        <Answer> Huntsville, AL. </Answer>
        <Answer> Macon. </Answer>
        <Answer> Savannah. </Answer>
        <Answer> Atlanta. </Answer>
        <Answer> Augusta. </Answer>
        <Answer> Mansfield,OH. </Answer>
        <Answer> Miami. </Answer>
        <Answer> Orlando. </Answer>
        <Answer> St. Petersburg. </Answer>
        <Answer> Panama City. </Answer>
        <Answer> Tampa. </Answer>
        <Answer> Tallahassee. </Answer>
        <Answer> Pensacola. </Answer>
        <Answer> Fort Myers. </Answer>
        <Answer> Columbia, SC. </Answer>
        <Answer> Charlotte, NC.</Answer>
        <Answer> Richmond, VA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Washington, DC.</Answer>
        <Answer> Baltimore, MD.</Answer>
        <Answer> Annapolis, MD. </Answer>
        <Answer> Asheville, NC. </Answer>
        <Answer> Raleigh, NC. </Answer>
        <Answer> Greensboro, NC.</Answer>
        <Answer> Roanoke, VA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Norfolk, VA.</Answer>
        <Answer>Knoxville, TN </Answer>
        <Answer> Nashville,TN</Answer>
        <Answer> Chattanooga, TN.</Answer>
        <Answer> Little Rock, AR.</Answer>
        <Answer> St Louis.</Answer>
        <Answer>Kansas City. </Answer>
        <Answer> Jefferson City, MO. </Answer>
        <Answer> Springfield, IL.</Answer>
        <Answer> Chicago.</Answer>
        <Answer> Effingham, IL. </Answer>
        <Answer> Terre Haute, IN.</Answer>
        <Answer> Indianapolis.</Answer>
        <Answer> Columbus, OH.</Answer>
        <Answer> Dayton, OH</Answer>
        <Answer> Cincinnati.</Answer>
        <Answer> Charleston, WV.</Answer>
        <Answer> Pittsburgh, PA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Philadelphia.</Answer>
        <Answer> Erie, PA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Wilmington, DE.</Answer>
        <Answer> Trenton , NJ.</Answer>
        <Answer> Newark, NJ.</Answer>
        <Answer> New York City.</Answer>
        <Answer> Providence.</Answer>
        <Answer> Hartford, CT.</Answer>
        <Answer> Boston, MA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Portland, ME.</Answer>
        <Answer> Harrisburg, PA.</Answer>
        <Answer> Albany, NY.</Answer>
        <Answer> Syracuse, NY.</Answer>
        <Answer> Buffalo.</Answer>
        <Answer> Augusta, ME.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bangor, ME.</Answer>
        <Answer> Montpelier, VT.</Answer>
        <Answer> Concord, NH.</Answer>
        <Answer> Ft. Wayne, IN.</Answer>
        <Answer> Ann Arbor, MI. </Answer>
        <Answer> Detroit.</Answer>
        <Answer> Lansing, MI.</Answer>
        <Answer> Milwaukee, WI.</Answer>
        <Answer> Madison, WI.</Answer>
        <Answer> Green Bay.</Answer>
        <Answer> Des Moines.</Answer>
        <Answer> Sioux City.</Answer>
        <Answer> Minneapolis.</Answer>
        <Answer> St Paul.</Answer>
        <Answer> Grand Forks, ND.</Answer>
        <Answer> Fargo, ND.</Answer>
        <Answer> Minot, ND.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bismarck, ND.</Answer>
        <Answer> Pierre, SD.</Answer>
        <Answer> Rapid City, SD.</Answer>
        <Answer> Omaha.</Answer>
        <Answer> Lincoln, NE.</Answer>
        <Answer> Topeka, KS.</Answer>
        <Answer> Salina, KS.</Answer>
        <Answer>Albuqueque. </Answer>
        <Answer>Santa Fe, NM. </Answer>
        <Answer>Phoenix. </Answer>
        <Answer> Flagstaff.</Answer>
        <Answer> Tucson.</Answer>
        <Answer> Salt Lake City.</Answer>
        <Answer> Provo, UT.</Answer>
        <Answer> Cheyenne. </Answer>
        <Answer> Casper, WY.</Answer>
        <Answer> Las Vegas.</Answer>
        <Answer> Reno.</Answer>
        <Answer> Twin Falls.</Answer>
        <Answer> Boise. </Answer>
        <Answer> Idaho Falls.</Answer>
        <Answer> Salem, OR.</Answer>
        <Answer> Portland, OR.</Answer>
        <Answer> Seattle.</Answer>
        <Answer> Medford, OR.</Answer>
        <Answer> Spokane.</Answer>
        <Answer> Vancouver, WA.</Answer>
        <Answer> San Diego.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bakersfield.</Answer>
        <Answer> Sacramento.</Answer>
        <Answer> Oakland.</Answer>
        <Answer> Helena, MT.</Answer>
        <Answer> Missoula. </Answer>
        <Answer> Billings. </Answer>
        <Answer> Vancouver.</Answer>
        <Answer> Winnipeg.</Answer>
        <Answer> Toronto.</Answer>
        <Answer> Montreal.</Answer>
        <Answer> Baton Rouge. </Answer>
        <Answer>San Antonio. </Answer>
        <Answer> Austin, TX.</Answer>
        <Answer> Amarillo.</Answer>
        <Answer> Corpus Christi.</Answer>
        <Answer> New Orleans.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you have your SA Hazmat permit? </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> Yes sir/ma'am got it right here.</Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
        <Answer> No, why do I need one?</Answer>
        <Answer> I don't sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer> Well yeah, you think I'd be stupid enough to haul HazMat with no permit?</Answer>
        <Answer> *shrugs* </Answer>
        <Answer>*searches* I don't seem to have it here. </Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
        <Answer> Yes. *hands you permit*</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you have 8 days of paper logs with you? </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> Yes I keep them here in my permit book. </Answer>
        <Answer>Why would I need to do that? </Answer>
        <Answer>I do *shows you* </Answer>
        <Answer>I'm sorry I don't. </Answer>
        <Answer> Yes sir/ma'am. *shows you*</Answer>
        <Answer> They're in my briefcase over here. </Answer>
        <Answer> Absolutely!</Answer>
        <Answer> Yeah I always keep them nearby.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hands over logs* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>What are you hauling today? (Reefer) </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>You probably don't wanna know. </Answer>
        <Answer>Paper goods. </Answer>
        <Answer>Frozen food. </Answer>
        <Answer>A bunch of groceries.</Answer>
        <Answer>Dollar pills store delivery. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cheese.</Answer>
        <Answer>Frozen chickens from cluckin bell.</Answer>
        <Answer> Fresh Produce.</Answer>
        <Answer> Groceries.</Answer>
        <Answer> Yogurt.</Answer>
        <Answer> Load of Sprunk.</Answer>
        <Answer> Load of Pibwasser.</Answer>
        <Answer> Flowers.</Answer>
        <Answer> Frozen Beef.</Answer>
        <Answer> I'm just paid to drive dude.</Answer>
        <Answer> Milk.</Answer>
        <Answer> Ice cream.</Answer>
        <Answer>Best not to ask too many questions. </Answer>
        <Answer> Chocolate.</Answer>
        <Answer> Coffee creamers.</Answer>
        <Answer> Almond milk.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hot dogs. </Answer>
        <Answer>Lunch meat. </Answer>
        <Answer> Turkeys. </Answer>
        <Answer> Eggs.</Answer>
        <Answer> Butter. </Answer>
        <Answer> Frozen baked goods.</Answer>
        <Answer> Pies.</Answer>
        <Answer> Pork.</Answer>
        <Answer>Veal. </Answer>
        <Answer>Ham. </Answer>
        <Answer>Chicken. </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>What are you hauling today? (Dry box) </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>You probably don't wanna know. </Answer>
        <Answer>Paper goods. </Answer>
        <Answer>School supplies. </Answer>
        <Answer>A bunch of dry groceries.</Answer>
        <Answer>Dollar pills store delivery. </Answer>
        <Answer>A lot of toilet paper, I hear it's in high demand.</Answer>
        <Answer>Clothing.</Answer>
        <Answer> Potatoes.</Answer>
        <Answer> Shoes and boots.</Answer>
        <Answer> Tobacco.</Answer>
        <Answer> Load of Sprunk.</Answer>
        <Answer> Load of Pibwasser.</Answer>
        <Answer> Giant paper rolls.</Answer>
        <Answer>Medical Supplies.</Answer>
        <Answer> I'm just paid to drive dude.</Answer>
        <Answer> Empty pallets.</Answer>
        <Answer> Beer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Best not to ask too many questions. </Answer>
        <Answer> Ketchup.</Answer>
        <Answer> Coffee</Answer>
        <Answer> Paper towels. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cleaning supplies.</Answer>
        <Answer> Hazardous materials</Answer>
        <Answer> Smart TV's. </Answer>
        <Answer> Electronics.</Answer>
        <Answer> Couches and chairs.</Answer>
        <Answer> Matresses.</Answer>
        <Answer> Amish furniture.</Answer>
        <Answer>Doors and windows. </Answer>
        <Answer> Empty bottles.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bottled water.</Answer>
        <Answer> Diet cola.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bread. </Answer>
        <Answer> Donuts.</Answer>
        <Answer> Vacum cleaners.</Answer>
        <Answer> Candy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Office supplies. </Answer>
        <Answer> Toys</Answer>
        <Answer> Mail.</Answer>
        <Answer>Newspapers. </Answer>
        <Answer>Paint. </Answer>
        <Answer> Automotive parts.</Answer>
        <Answer>Carpet. </Answer>
        <Answer>Tires. </Answer>
        <Answer>Barrels of HazMat. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cookies. </Answer>
        <Answer>Energy drinks. </Answer>
        <Answer>Potato chips. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cosmetics. </Answer>
        <Answer> Dry groceries.</Answer>
        <Answer> Bottled water. </Answer>
        <Answer> Fishing gear.</Answer>
        <Answer>Cereal. </Answer>
        <Answer> Cola.</Answer>
        <Answer> Camping gear.</Answer>
        <Answer> Motor oil. *HazMat*</Answer>
        <Answer> Propane. *HazMat* </Answer>
        <Answer> Hardware supplies. </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>What are you hauling today? (Flatbed) </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Lumber. </Answer>
        <Answer>Drywall.</Answer>
        <Answer>Steel coils. </Answer>
        <Answer>Construction equipment.</Answer>
        <Answer>Aluminum coils. </Answer>
        <Answer> Tractors.</Answer>
        <Answer> Concrete barriers.</Answer>
        <Answer> Onions.</Answer>
        <Answer> Fencing..</Answer>
        <Answer> Steel beams.</Answer>
        <Answer> Roofing material.</Answer>
        <Answer>Palletized sacks of sand. </Answer>
        <Answer> Siding. </Answer>
        <Answer>Shingles. </Answer>
        <Answer> Potting soil.</Answer>
        <Answer>Landscaping stones. </Answer>
        <Answer> Construction equipment. </Answer>
        <Answer> Roof air conditioners.</Answer>
        <Answer> Shipping containers.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Do you have an overweight permit?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Uhhh, Nope. </Answer>
        <Answer> I didn't even know it was overweight. </Answer>
        <Answer> I totally forgot to check this load. </Answer>
        <Answer> I wish. HAHA</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure do. *hands you permit* </Answer>
        <Answer>I'm afraid not. </Answer>
        <Answer> Well this is not going to be a good day I see. </Answer>
        <Answer>Who do I call for that? </Answer>
        <Answer> Yes officer. *hands you permit* </Answer>
        <Answer>No, This is not the way I planned for this trip. </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>

    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Inspection Statements~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Driver, I need you to pull up on the scales.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> *Pulls on scales* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Paper logs are required in case your ELOG malfunctions.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> I'm sorry, I was not aware of that. </Answer>
        <Answer>Oh I see, well I'll pick some up ASAP </Answer>
        <Answer>I left them at home accidentally. </Answer>
        <Answer> Well, I guess that makes sense? </Answer>
        <Answer> Why do they make us do this crap if it don't even work then?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well back in my day, paper logs NEVER malfuntioned. </Answer>
        <Answer> I used to carry plenty of paper logs, 2 or 3 books at a time. HAHA</Answer>
        <Answer>Time for me to go home and get a factory job, sick of this crap! </Answer>
        <Answer> Yeah, and steering wheel holders need GPS, or they will malfunction. </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>I'm going to dip your fuel tank.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Why you need to do that? </Answer>
        <Answer>Whatever you got to do. </Answer>
        <Answer>Can you hurry up, I need to go. </Answer>
        <Answer>*knods* </Answer>
        <Answer>Aren't you just a nosy SOB </Answer>
        <Answer>Don't worry, I pay all your stupid taxes. </Answer>
        <Answer>Is that your job? </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>

    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Inspection Actions~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Inspect logbook Papers and ELOG~s~ </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>11 hour violation *previous day*</Answer>
        <Answer>30 minute break violation today</Answer>
        <Answer>30 minute break violation *previous day* </Answer>
        <Answer>14 hour violation *today*</Answer>
        <Answer>70 hour violation </Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>14 hour violation *previous day*</Answer>
        <Answer>Personal Conveyance Violation *Possible Falsification* </Answer>
        <Answer>11/14/70 hour violations </Answer>
        <Answer>11 hour violation *today* </Answer>
        <Answer>Failure to certify previous day logs</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS </Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
        <Answer>NO VIOLATIONS</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Check Permits ~s~ </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer>
        VALID </Answer>
        <Answer>Expired fuel tax</Answer>- <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> No fuel
        tax</Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer>
        VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> Annual Inspection Out of Date</Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer>
        VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> No annual inspection</Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
        <Answer> VALID </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Check Bills of Lading~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes sir/ma'am got'em right here. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>Absolutely officer. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hands over paperwork* </Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that no problem. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Hands you paperwork* </Answer>
        <Answer>I'm actually empty at the moment.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes sir/ma'am got'em right here! *Hands you paperwork* </Answer>
        <Answer>Yes officer. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew you would ask, here you go. *Hands you paperwork*</Answer>
        <Answer>*searches for paperwork* Here you go!</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Inspect for red dye in the off-road diesel fuel.~s~ </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>RED</Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>RED </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>RED</Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
        <Answer>GREEN </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Inspection Weighing~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Box trucks 26K Max</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> 15,000 </Answer>
        <Answer>16,000 </Answer>
        <Answer>19,223 </Answer>
        <Answer>19,432 </Answer>
        <Answer>19,700 </Answer>
        <Answer> 26,500</Answer>
        <Answer> 20,321</Answer>
        <Answer>28,080 </Answer>
        <Answer>17,100 </Answer>
        <Answer>17,245 </Answer>
        <Answer> 17,399</Answer>
        <Answer>17,401 </Answer>
        <Answer>17,554 </Answer>
        <Answer> 17,680</Answer>
        <Answer> 17,700</Answer>
        <Answer> 17,877</Answer>
        <Answer> 17,900</Answer>
        <Answer>18,055 </Answer>
        <Answer> 18,200</Answer>
        <Answer>18,375 </Answer>
        <Answer> 18,423</Answer>
        <Answer> 18,532</Answer>
        <Answer>18,699 </Answer>
        <Answer>28,069 </Answer>
        <Answer>18,799 </Answer>
        <Answer> 18,854</Answer>
        <Answer>18,902 </Answer>
        <Answer>19,444 </Answer>
        <Answer> 19,500</Answer>
        <Answer> 19,610</Answer>
        <Answer>29,655 </Answer>
        <Answer>19,767 </Answer>
        <Answer> 19,788</Answer>
        <Answer> 19,833</Answer>
        <Answer> 19,925</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,723</Answer>
        <Answer>20,072 </Answer>
        <Answer>20,199 </Answer>
        <Answer>20,255 </Answer>
        <Answer>20,300 </Answer>
        <Answer>20,310 </Answer>
        <Answer> 20,429</Answer>
        <Answer> 26,800</Answer>
        <Answer>26,922 </Answer>
        <Answer>27,325 </Answer>
        <Answer>20,525 </Answer>
        <Answer> 20,612</Answer>
        <Answer> 20,744</Answer>
        <Answer> 20,816</Answer>
        <Answer>20,988 </Answer>
        <Answer>21,015 </Answer>
        <Answer>28,112 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,233</Answer>
        <Answer> 26,655</Answer>
        <Answer>27,500 </Answer>
        <Answer> 27,998</Answer>
        <Answer>21,109 </Answer>
        <Answer>21,253 </Answer>
        <Answer> 21,444</Answer>
        <Answer> 21,575</Answer>
        <Answer> 21,600 </Answer>
        <Answer> 21,732</Answer>
        <Answer> 21,810</Answer>
        <Answer>21,955 </Answer>
        <Answer>22,050 </Answer>
        <Answer>22,123 </Answer>
        <Answer>22,276 </Answer>
        <Answer>22,345 </Answer>
        <Answer> 22,497</Answer>
        <Answer>22,515 </Answer>
        <Answer> 22,699</Answer>
        <Answer> 22,710</Answer>
        <Answer>22,805 </Answer>
        <Answer> 22,900</Answer>
        <Answer> 23,154 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,275 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,377 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,402 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,599 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,612 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,700 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,886 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,150 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,013 </Answer>
        <Answer> 27,155 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,266 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,547 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,599 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,613 </Answer>
        <Answer> 27,532 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,800 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,544 </Answer>
        <Answer> 24,812 </Answer>
        <Answer> 25,123 </Answer>
        <Answer> 25,999 </Answer>
        <Answer> 26,321 </Answer>
        <Answer> 26,500 </Answer>
        <Answer> 19,997 </Answer>
        <Answer> 23,176 </Answer>
        <Answer> 25,044 </Answer>
        <Answer> 15,432 </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Truck/Trailer 12k/34k/34k max ~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Steer axle </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> 11,225 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,700 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,000 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,553 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,887 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,950 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,300 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,630 </Answer>
        <Answer> 13,000 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,475 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,815 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,999 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,800 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,810 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,820 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,830</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,840</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,850</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,910 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,920 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,930</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,940 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,950 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,150 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,250 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,350</Answer>
        <Answer> 12,450 </Answer>
        <Answer> 12,550</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,700 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,750</Answer>
        <Answer> 11,850 </Answer>
        <Answer> 11,987 </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Drive axle</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> 31,088</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,125</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,276 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,345 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,499</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,503</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,622 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,785</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,865 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,900 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,099 </Answer>
        <Answer> 35,110 </Answer>
        <Answer> 34,800 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,199 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,237 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,354</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,699 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,715 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,866 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 36,555</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,015</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,020</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,175</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,778</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,455</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,010</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,300</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,200</Answer>
        <Answer> 38,099</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,667 </Answer>
        <Answer> 33,815 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,520</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,444 </Answer>
        <Answer> 26,045</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,567</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,743</Answer>
        <Answer> 36,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,040 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,110 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,259</Answer>
        <Answer> 28,360 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,412</Answer>
        <Answer> 28,575</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,699</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,750</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,132</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,277</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,400</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,010</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,990</Answer>
        <Answer> 37,450</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,635</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,735</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,635</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,855</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,723</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,900</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,813</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,701</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,600</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,100</Answer>

      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Trailer Axle </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> 31,088</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,125</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,276 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,345 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,499</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,503</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,622 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,785</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,865 </Answer>
        <Answer> 31,900 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,099 </Answer>
        <Answer> 35,110 </Answer>
        <Answer> 34,800 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,199 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,237 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,354</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,699 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,715 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,866 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 36,555</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,015</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,020</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,175</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,778</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,455</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,010</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,300</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,200</Answer>
        <Answer> 38,099</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,667 </Answer>
        <Answer> 33,815 </Answer>
        <Answer> 32,520</Answer>
        <Answer> 31,444 </Answer>
        <Answer> 26,045</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,567</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,743</Answer>
        <Answer> 36,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 27,040 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,110 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,259</Answer>
        <Answer> 28,360 </Answer>
        <Answer> 28,412</Answer>
        <Answer> 28,575</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,699</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,750</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,132</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,277</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,400</Answer>
        <Answer> 35,010</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,990</Answer>
        <Answer> 37,128</Answer>
        <Answer> 37,450</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,635</Answer>
        <Answer> 32,735</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,635</Answer>
        <Answer> 33,855</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,723</Answer>
        <Answer> 34,900</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,999</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,813</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,701</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,600</Answer>
        <Answer> 29,100</Answer>

      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Equipment~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Tractor~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Brakes</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Right rear brake can is caged off</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Left rear brake can is caged off</Answer>
        <Answer> Front pads below legal minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear pads below legal minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Tires</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> Left rear low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Right rear low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Front left steer low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Front right steer low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear left below minimum tread </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear right below minimum tread </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear left flat spot showing cords </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear right flat spot showing cords </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Steer tires below minimum tread </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear left tire is flat </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear right tire is flat </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Air System</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Leak at air tank </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Leak at rear left chamber </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Leak at rear right chamber </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~g~Trailer~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Brakes </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Front axle slack adjuster backed off </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear axle slack adjuster backed off </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Front left can caged off</Answer>
        <Answer> Rear left can caged off </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Front right can caged off</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed but brakes very hot* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear right can caged off</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Front axle pads below minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> Rear axle pads below minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer>Front left brake is cracked </Answer>
        <Answer> Rear right brake is cracked</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Tires *LEFT/REAR/INSIDE Etc.*</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> L/F/O low air pessure </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F/I low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/O low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/I low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/O low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/I low air pressure</Answer>
        <Answer> L/R/O low air pressure</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/R/I low air pressure </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F/O Tread below minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F/I tread below minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> L/R/O tread below minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/R/I tread below minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/O tread below minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/I tread below minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/O tread below minimum </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/I tread below minimum</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F/I tire is flat </Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/O tire is flat </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/O tire is flat </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R/I tire is showing cords</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F/I tire is showing cords</Answer>
        <Answer> L/R/O tire is showing cords</Answer>
        <Answer> R/F/O tire is showing cords</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F wheel lug nuts loose</Answer>
        <Answer> R/R wheel lug nuts loose</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Inspect Air System </Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer> Red air line is cracked </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Blue air line is cracked</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Air lines dragging under trailer, hole found </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> Leak at air tank </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/F chamber is leakinng</Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> L/R chamber is leaking</Answer>
        <Answer> R/F chamber is leaking </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> *Passed* </Answer>
        <Answer> R/R chamber is leaking </Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="TRAFFIC STOP: ENDING">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Ending Intro~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Sorry for the wait, here is your stuff back.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Thank You.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thanks, I appreciate it.</Answer>
        <Answer>So what is the verdict your honor?</Answer>
        <Answer>I can't wait to hear your ruling.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was beginning to think you died back there.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you stop and take lunch while you were back there?</Answer>
        <Answer>I have no choice but to wait.</Answer>
        <Answer>No trouble at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>What do you cops do back there that takes so long?</Answer>
        <Answer>Why does it take so long, Im just curious.</Answer>
        <Answer>No other units showed up so Im happy about that.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's not like im in a big rush huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Probably playing that LSPDFR on the computer huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>It's all good officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not going to lie I was getting kind of worried.</Answer>
        <Answer>What the hell took you so long?</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you go look me up and stalk my social media accounts?</Answer>
        <Answer>As they say just Chive On or something hippie like that.</Answer>
        <Answer>You probably have dial up internet in that car huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you REALLY sorry though, I'm just joking with you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have no choice but to wait.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure, Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just doing my part to be a good citizen.</Answer>
        <Answer>So how much do you know about me?</Answer>
        <Answer>Excellent, I hope it's in the order I gave it to you in.</Answer>
        <Answer>I nearly used up all my data waiting for you to get done.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you single I got a cousin that would find you adorable.</Answer>
        <Answer>Life seems like all you do is wait, just one long waiting game.</Answer>
        <Answer>Did you atleast follow me on Instagram?</Answer>
        <Answer>It's no problem at all.</Answer>
        <Answer>My father is a retired cop so I appreciate all you do.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you have a warning for me, I might need to ask you out.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Snarls*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep, Yep, time is money but your broke ass wouldn't know.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Citing Endings~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[CITE] This is for the failure to wear your seat belt.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Is that really necessary?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I learned my lesson.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's a first for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was irresponsible, I understand.</Answer>
        <Answer>In a pandemic you write me a ticket for over $100?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to have to work like 2 hours of O.T. for this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really wish I could've gotten a warning.</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh well, it is what it is.</Answer>
        <Answer>I see you decided to be a jerk.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks at you and nods*</Answer>
        <Answer>A simple warning would have been all that I needed.</Answer>
        <Answer>I deserve it.</Answer>
        <Answer>That works for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>It shouldn't be over $100 right?</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[CITE] You'll be getting multiple tickets for _____ alright?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Is that really necessary?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do you really have to cite me for every little thing?</Answer>
        <Answer>I am going to have to work like 20 hours of O.T. for this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have child support to pay and now these crazy fines.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am one check away from bankruptcy and you've ruined me.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are as cold as the steel on those handcuffs huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>So you decided this is the best way to learn my lesson?</Answer>
        <Answer>Please I know you can cut me a break if you wanted.</Answer>
        <Answer>I suck at being an adult Im sorry.</Answer>
        <Answer>I need to do much better with my responsibilities huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>You are a devil from the pits of hell!</Answer>
        <Answer>Please I just lost my job last week.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can barely pay for my kids lunch as it is.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can you cut me some slack?</Answer>
        <Answer>You guys are the worst money hungry cops I know.</Answer>
        <Answer>I made a few mistakes though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Lay it on me then.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fair enough.</Answer>
        <Answer>I really really cant afford that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure why not throw the whole book at me.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[CITE] Your citation today will be for ___ okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*looks sad*</Answer>
        <Answer>Let's get this show on the road okay?</Answer>
        <Answer>I couldn't agree more.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem my kids can eat Ramen noodles for a week.</Answer>
        <Answer>Amazing how you just spent so much of my money for me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will most certainly see you in court.</Answer>
        <Answer>I have no choice I suppose?</Answer>
        <Answer>Whatever.</Answer>
        <Answer>It is what it is huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hate you pigs nothing personal though.</Answer>
        <Answer>Well their goes my insurance rates.</Answer>
        <Answer>*looks at you*</Answer>
        <Answer>That sucks but I understand.</Answer>
        <Answer>I dont believe I deserve this.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks upset*</Answer>
        <Answer>I got warnings before so I guess this is fair.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess you're not one of the cool cops huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Just as hungry for my money as you are for doughnuts I see.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will be seeing you in court on this.</Answer>
        <Answer>You just had to give me the ticket huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>*Sighs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Wow no break can be caught.</Answer>
        <Answer>CAn a supervisor over turn this or something?</Answer>
        <Answer>Hope your probable cause was solid, my lawyer is good.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you say so.</Answer>
        <Answer>Okay what all do I need to know about this?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I need any other information?</Answer>
        <Answer>MHHHMMMM.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] Watch your speed, no break today sorry.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Well I guess that means we dont eat for a week!</Answer>
        <Answer>Gee thanks for nothing officer</Answer>
        <Answer>You are right and I was wrong.</Answer>
        <Answer>I could have hurt myself or someone else huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure whatever.</Answer>
        <Answer>I still appreciate your service.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are just doing your job.</Answer>
        <Answer>I broke the law and i shouldnt get a break.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hopefully this will make me learn my lesson.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess I got the jerk today.</Answer>
        <Answer>Better than going to jail I guess, I'll take it</Answer>
        <Answer>*mutters* Thats fucked up man</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Warning Endings~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[WARN] No ticket for the seat belt today.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Yes officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>I appreciate the warning.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so glad you didn't give me a ticket for that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you so much!</Answer>
        <Answer>Awesome, I appreciate the break.</Answer>
        <Answer>It would've been a dumb ticket anyway.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hey! I caught a break for once.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're too kind.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[WARN] I'm just going to give you a warning okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Appreciate that I really do.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are a saint you have no idea.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is what I was hoping for.</Answer>
        <Answer>Really?</Answer>
        <Answer>BOOM! that's what Im talking about.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hell Yeah.</Answer>
        <Answer>That's bitchin.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fabulous! I love that we are seeing eye to eye.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are the best.</Answer>
        <Answer>Fack Yeah!</Answer>
        <Answer>That really means the world to me.</Answer>
        <Answer>I caught a break for once in my life.</Answer>
        <Answer>Bless your heart officer</Answer>
        <Answer>Alrighty then! Jim Carey pet detective haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is the kinda service I expect from you cops.</Answer>
        <Answer>You didn't have to do that but I thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Look at that I finally caught a break.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is A-OKAY with me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Just what I was hoping for.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am going to buy a lotto ticket if I win I'll spilt it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I could kiss you but I'm sure neither of us want that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Outstanding I can get on with my day now.</Answer>
        <Answer>I couldn't ask for more.</Answer>
        <Answer>Great news... the justice system works huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>A warning is fine with me.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[WARN] I'll be letting you slide with a warning.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I appreciate that so much!</Answer>
        <Answer>No words have ever been sweeter.</Answer>
        <Answer>Hey I can't argue with that.</Answer>
        <Answer>My dad served on the force 22 years and you remind me of him.</Answer>
        <Answer>Woot!</Answer>
        <Answer>I was not going to be happy if I got a ticket by the way.</Answer>
        <Answer>How can people not love you guys?</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess the quota is already filled huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Hmm I may have to do it again then.</Answer>
        <Answer>Good way to start off my week.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is a ticket I could not afford to get.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for not being a jerk cop.</Answer>
        <Answer>I thank you for your service, keep doing a good job.</Answer>
        <Answer>For once a true public servant.</Answer>
        <Answer>Would have preferred you never stop me in the first place.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am very thankful for your kidness officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is GREAT news.</Answer>
        <Answer>So happy not to be a victim of your quota.</Answer>
        <Answer>Your boss wont like that but my wallet loves you.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are an honorable enforcer of the law, thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>All I do is Win!</Answer>
        <Answer>I love how you have been so kind with me.</Answer>
        <Answer>It's not like I couldn't afford it anyway.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~leniency Endings~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[CITE] I'm feeling nice, You'll only be cited for ___ okay?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Gleefull smile* THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU!</Answer>
        <Answer>Awesome.</Answer>
        <Answer>I would hate to see when you are feeling mad haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>So glad I got you on one of your nice days.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm glad you see me as a person and not a money tree.</Answer>
        <Answer>I was so foolish and I am sorry for how I drove.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm so happy to know cops like you are around here.</Answer>
        <Answer>Halleleujah, praise Jesus!</Answer>
        <Answer>I see my patience paid off.</Answer>
        <Answer>I love that... respect given is respect earned.</Answer>
        <Answer>You're doing a wonderful job.</Answer>
        <Answer>You have saved me so much of a headache with this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not sure why you did it, but I am very happy.</Answer>
        <Answer>I knew all you guys werent bad at all</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Smiles*</Answer>
        <Answer>This really helped me more than you know.</Answer>
        <Answer>How about no citation hehe?</Answer>
        <Answer>That is very kind of you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for serving the people of the city.</Answer>
        <Answer>You just saved me so much money thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>I could kiss you officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>See I knew deep down some of you have a heart.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are AMAZEBALLS!</Answer>
        <Answer>I love a person who takes pride in their job.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for treating me with respect today.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[SPEED] You were going __ over, but im citing you for __ mph out of leniency.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Wow I am so happy about that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for cutting me a break.</Answer>
        <Answer>I didnt know you could be that kind.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm lost for words, Thank You.</Answer>
        <Answer>OMG you just saved me like $300</Answer>
        <Answer>My parents are still going to kill me.</Answer>
        <Answer>That was so stupid and I won't do it again.</Answer>
        <Answer>You are the best.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Citation/Ticket Signature~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[COURT] You are to pay the fine or appear in court as indicated.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I understand... sorry again my mistake</Answer>
        <Answer>Keep going.</Answer>
        <Answer>Who comes up with the prices of these fines?</Answer>
        <Answer>The state must think we all earn six figures.</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance ya'll have a payment plan?</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm going to need an installment plan to pay this off.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for the warning.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes I am following along.</Answer>
        <Answer>I imagine I can pay this online somehow?</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope I dont have to miss work to pay this.</Answer>
        <Answer>I will pay the fine no problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>Looks like I might try to fight this.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh-huh..</Answer>
        <Answer>I got that.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods in agreement*.</Answer>
        <Answer>How much is the penalty? DAAAAAAMMMMN time to move!</Answer>
        <Answer>Is it too late for you to just give me a warning? Im joking</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[COURT] Failure to do this will turn into a warrant.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Really over an infraction? Guess I better take care of this fast.</Answer>
        <Answer>I know I have seen it happen to my cousin when she didnt pay it.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is crazy.</Answer>
        <Answer>That is the last thing I want is a warrant.</Answer>
        <Answer>I guess you always could bring me before a magistrate now huh?</Answer>
        <Answer>Understood.</Answer>
        <Answer>I understand and intend to cooperate fully, thank you for your service.</Answer>
        <Answer>My brother forgot and got arrested over a turn signal ticket.</Answer>
        <Answer>I work near the court house... so I should be fine.</Answer>
        <Answer>Please just give me warning. This wont ever happen again, I swear.</Answer>
        <Answer>Had that happen to me back in 2010.</Answer>
        <Answer>Had that happen to my mom last year.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am taking care of that ASAP.</Answer>
        <Answer>A warrant for not paying a bogus ticket?</Answer>
        <Answer>Last thing I want is DOG the bounty hunter knocking on my door!</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh I will get it taken care of.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not going to jail over a ticket.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you for the warning.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[COURT] Sign here to acknowledge you received it.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>No problem. *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I usually don't sign anything with out my lawyer *Signs ticket*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I am ready to leave *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>No I will not. *Refuses* (Use REFUSE question to let them reconsider).</Answer>
        <Answer>Now I have to give you my autograph too? *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Signs the ticket*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>(*Refuses to sign* Choose to let them go or use REFUSE question.)</Answer>
        <Answer>I received it *Signs ticket*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Are we done yet *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>If it gets you to leave *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>(*Refuses to sign* Choose to let them go or use REFUSE question.)</Answer>
        <Answer>If it will shut you up *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>My pleasure *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I just want to go home *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I acknowledge it.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Signs quickly*</Answer>
        <Answer>I dont want any trouble *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>It seems good to me. *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I deff don't want to sit here all day *Signs ticket*.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks over the ticket and signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>This is all legit you say? *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Signs* I will see you in court I hate to say.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Looks for a pen and Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>(*Refuses to sign* Choose to let them go or use REFUSE question.)</Answer>
        <Answer>Any chance you can rip this up? *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Rips up the ticket* (Arrest them for obstuction)</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh goody *Signs ticket*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Ouch this is going to hurt *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Refuses to sign* (Use REFUSE question to let them reconsider)</Answer>
        <Answer>My pleasure *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I just want to go home *Signs*</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>[REFUSE] Refusal to sign the ticket is arrestable.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's my right but I will waive it *signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Screw that *signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>(Refuses again but it's your choice)</Answer>
        <Answer>Oh its like that huh? *signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I regret my decision *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I go now, I'm not signing it. (Arrest them)</Answer>
        <Answer>I am not willing to go to jail *Signs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Signs it*</Answer>
        <Answer>Ughhhhh *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just hangry *Signs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Looks like you better cuff me (Arrest them)</Answer>
        <Answer>Are you kidding me right now? *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm not guilty! (Arrest them)</Answer>
        <Answer>(Refuses again but it's your choice)</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright I'll take the ticket *Signs*.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sorry for my outburst *Signs*</Answer>
        <Answer>(Refuses again but it's your choice)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>~r~Ending Statements~s~</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>(Just a Section Seperator)</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Any other questions for me at this time?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Nope.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not that I can think of.</Answer>
        <Answer>That will be all.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I go now?</Answer>
        <Answer>No officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Buckles seat belt*</Answer>
        <Answer>Not really.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not at this time.</Answer>
        <Answer>If you dont make the court date the ticket is dismissed right?</Answer>
        <Answer>How do you sleep at night?</Answer>
        <Answer>No, You seemed pretty thourough.</Answer>
        <Answer>No, You explained it well.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Have a better rest of your day.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It's off to a pretty bad start.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep I will.</Answer>
        <Answer>I am going to try to.</Answer>
        <Answer>If I don't see you again that will make it better.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can I go now?</Answer>
        <Answer>Enough with the chit chat please.</Answer>
        <Answer>You too *calls you by your name on the ticket*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods*</Answer>
        <Answer>When do I take off?</Answer>
        <Answer>Do I wait for you to pull off or what?</Answer>
        <Answer>Well I hope that is possible.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope so.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure it will be that easy.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure that is going to happen.</Answer>
        <Answer>You sure did your part, thank you.</Answer>
        <Answer>Nah this day is pretty much ruined.</Answer>
        <Answer>Not sure how I am going to make this better.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>You're free to go when I get back to my vehicle.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Sounds good.</Answer>
        <Answer>Be safe out there.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Nods Yes*</Answer>
        <Answer>*Waves*</Answer>
        <Answer>Yep.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Keep up the good work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope you make it home safely today.</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Stay safe out here.</Answer>
        <Answer>No problem.</Answer>
        <Answer>Stay safe out there.</Answer>
        <Answer>Eat a doughnut for me later.</Answer>
        <Answer>Best thing I have heard all day.</Answer>
        <Answer>You got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'm just happy to not be in your backseat haha.</Answer>
        <Answer>Drive safely.</Answer>
        <Answer>Great.</Answer>
        <Answer>Your lights are so bright I can't see behind me.</Answer>
        <Answer>Can you honk to let me know when it is safe?</Answer>
        <Answer>No problemo.</Answer>
        <Answer>Uh-huh.</Answer>
        <Answer>Alright, later.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Smiles*</Answer>
        <Answer>I got it.</Answer>
        <Answer>Awesome.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question>Be Careful merging back into traffic.</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>*Waves*.</Answer>
        <Answer>I do not want to wreck my car.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>Understood.</Answer>
        <Answer>*Is quiet*</Answer>
        <Answer>You know it.</Answer>
        <Answer>I can do that.</Answer>
        <Answer>Keep up the good work.</Answer>
        <Answer>I hope you make it home to your family later.</Answer>
        <Answer>Yes officer.</Answer>
        <Answer>You know it.</Answer>
        <Answer>This makes me nervous.</Answer>
        <Answer>Sure.</Answer>
        <Answer>I'll be careful.</Answer>
        <Answer>Thank you again.</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
</TrafficStopQuestions>